<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-02-01T11:29:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">山猪</title><subtitle>方寸之间 点滴墨彩</subtitle><entry><title type="html">英文邮件</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english-email/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="英文邮件" /><published>2020-01-29T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2020-01-29T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english-email</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english-email/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.learnenglishwithwill.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/04/emails-040419.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- more --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;e.g.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Happy new year! - I hope you and your family had a great holiday and enjoyed some well deserved time off. Thank you again for the terrific effort and a strong result last year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Hi Steven,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;It is my pleasure to talk with you earlier today. Thank you for contacting xxxx.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I am writing to share more information with you about xxxx and our digital signage system. The attached brochure will provide you with an overview of our post popular system features. You can also learn more by our website at xxx.com. As you will see, xxxx has been providing industry-leading signage system for past 25 years and we are honored to have our system in place with over 2,500 hotels, resort and casino around the world. We would be interested in exploring a relationship with xxx in order to explore digital signage opportunities in China. As I’ve mentioned, our primary customer focus is with hotels, resorts, casinos. Our digital display system is designed to meet the needs of the hospitality market. We are fortunate to have earned the prefered vendor status with many of the leading hotel brands including: …… and many more. Please let me know if you have relationships with any hotels and we can develop a plan to pursue the opportunity together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Please review our information at your earliest convenience and let me know if you have any questions. I look forward to our next communication.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Regards,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;xxxx&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Email etiquette&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Thanks for the quick reply.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Thanks for getting back to me.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;THanks for the update on the situation.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Thanks for the updated information.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Thanks for gathering the information this week on this issue.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;simple reply&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Thank you.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Well noted.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Noted/Received with thanks.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Good information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kind Attn.: Mr. Jack Wey– General Manager (hope I would be the GM one day)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Subject: XXXXX Cooperation/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Mr. Jack Wey&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[Your company] is the main [your product] manufacturer in China since 1968, our major clients are[those have very good reputation and renown companies in the field that have direct or indirect biz with your company, i.e. IBM, SONY .. ].&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We believe that you can rely on us as we provide you quite satisfactory service and products with best quality at most competitive price in the world. We are very happy if you do not hesitate to send us any of your inquiries and we will always give satisfactory services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Products: (product range)
Standards: (product design standard, if any)
Service: (product applicable field, function)
Size: (don’t fuckingly tell your client you don’t know)
Etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Certificates: (certificates that your company got)
Annual Sales Turnover: ( just list some number here,)
Staff No.staff no of your company, if your company is big, if not, omit this point)
Cover of Land list some number here)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to hearing from you at your convenience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks &amp;amp; best regards,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.S. I am attaching our product catalogue/scope of service for your future reference in my following email to you, please kindly check.
( please don’t send your product catalogue in the email, you are telling him here is showing your respect to him that you are sending good info to him,but not spam, therefore, you better send another email to your client with your product catalogue. Your client will check it if your products are of him/her interest)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;YOUR NAME
POSITION
DEPARTMENT
COMPANY NAME
ADD
TEL
MOBILE
FAX
EMAIL
WEB&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear all, I am jack wey, this above mentioned email for marketing is only one sample to your general potential clients, it would be revised accordingly to different clients.
Kindly be informed that email marketing is mainly depending on your SET title, therefore pls try to improve TO SET THE TITLE OF YOUR EMAIL.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;（开发信的成功与否，跟开发信内容的大少无关，关键是你怎么把涉及到客户每一个利益、兴趣都说到，能连起来，他都会像继续看下去，要不我们还看电视连续剧干嘛？)
邮件开发成功与否与以下几个方面有关（个人认为）：（按主次顺序）&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;邮件标题（要是我，邮件标题一看就知道是推销的，I am sorry, please fuck off and stay in my trash box）&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;邮件内容是否吸引/对客户是否有效，有利可图；客户是否感兴趣.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;所联系的人的职位和权利（Pls send to the RIGHT PERSON）&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;发信人日后沟通技巧，plus&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;以上的开发信只是针对任意一家公司，如果要想开发信更成功，你就得研究或者了解一下这个公司的情况再发。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;有的开发信中，并不能把所有东西都一一列出来，所以一天发个100封的开发信的人，一天很难记下前天发给谁了，日后很难去跟踪，也不知道自己以前说了什么，如果是这样，最好做个记录；邮件已发出3天之内，马上再发一封邮件跟踪，过2如没有回复，再发一封了解，第三封邮件刚发后30分钟，马上给个电话。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;记住，成功的开发信，一般要有电话跟踪才能比较有效果，当然有幸运的人，或是客户也正好有询价，有货采购才会直接跟你联系，所以为什么要日后电话沟通的原因。现在一般一个客户一天能收到很多信，你只有电话过去了，说明你请况，他才知道你是谁，什么公司，下次在电话的时候，他会说“oh, Jack? Jack wey from China,XXX company? Oh, how are you? …..”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;开发信模板(二)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Mr. JACK,
Thank you for your e-mail &amp;amp; I do appreciate the content.（讲得是我开发信的内容）
I do not have any hesitation to start business with your esteemed company.对我公司感兴趣
Thus I ask you kindly to arrange courier me full set of all your catalogs in one binder along with copies of all your certificates , end user approvals ,..etc. 需要一些文件进一步合作&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, I would like to hear from you in details about your previous operation in middle east area .
Do you have agent,distributer,..etc?想成为我们代理分销商&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Best Regards
XXXXXXXXXXXXX&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;现在说说我开发信主要的信息：
标题： Mr. XXX + 他公司的名称 （点名道姓和公司，一目了然）
内容：
MOrning！ Mr. XXXXXX&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is Jack, Sales Manager from a well established PRODUCT manufacturer in China. Hope I reach the right person at the right time to talk about PRODUCT cooperation and strategies for your company?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did a little bit research on your company and I’m sure you would be continuously looking at opportunities to expand your product supplying scope/services and make it as the brand to own your company reputation in the PRODUCT market and increase your market return with your constant efforts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can fulfill any of your business needs and maximize your business profits compared with lots of PRODUCT manufacturers as we are newly launching DDDD brand PRODUCT in international market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our business reference includes:
? 20 years appointed OEM for EU,USA PRODUCT manufacturers
? Approvals from …….(主要客户，最好是国际同行知名企业)…
? 70%~80% products for international application
(for more details, please contact us) 这个地方用黄色文字背景，突出公司优势&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the GM of 客户公司名称 , it is your responsibility to find a sustainable and trustworthy business partner relationship and ensure a promising company future. 我的公司 is interested in cooperating with you to uncover the PRODUCT demand of 客户市场 market from now on. As you have experiences in PROCUT, it would be easier to seize the opportunity to win great PRODUCT demand in 客户市场。
（这里很明显的标示你的合作意图和对客户公司的了解及所联系人的职责所在，没有人会反对你强调他的职责和利益）&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hope to have your excited feedback TODAY.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks ®ards,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JACK
24 hours available for you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;请求建立商业关系
Rogers Chemical Supply Co. 10E.22Street Omaha8, Neb Gentlemen: We have obtained your name and address from Aristo Shoes, Milan, and we are writing to enquire whether you would be willing to establish business relations with us. We have been importers of shoes for many years. At present, We are interested in extending our, range and would appreciate your catalogues and quotations. If your prices were competitive we would expect to transact a significant volume of business. We look forward to your early reply.Very truly yours 自米兰职权里斯托鞋类公司取得贵公司和地址，特此修函，祈能发展关系。多年来，本公司经营鞋类进口生意，现欲扩展业务范围。盼能惠赐商品目录和报价表。 如价格公道，本公司必大额订购。 烦请早日赐复。 此致&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2.回复对方建立商业关系的请求
Thank your for your letter of the 16th of this month. We shall be glad to enter into business relations with your company. In compliance with your request, we are sending you, under separate cover, our latest catalogue and price list covering our export range. Payment should be made by irrevocable and confirmed letter of credit. Should you wish to place an order, please telex or fax us. 本月16日收到有关商务关系的来函，不胜欣喜。谨遵要求另函奉上最新之出口商品目录和报价单。款项烦请以不可撤销保兑之信用状支付。如欲订货，请电传或传真为盼。 此致 敬礼&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;请求担任独家代理
We would like to inform you that we act on a sole agency basis for a number of manufacturers. We specialize in finished cotton goods for the Middle eastern market: Our activities cover all types of household linen. Until now, we have been working with your textiles department and our collaboration has proved to be mutually beneficial. Please refer to them for any information regarding our company. We are very interested in an exclusive arrangement with your factory for the promotion of your products in Bahrain. We look forward to your early reply. `本公司担任多家厂家的独家代理，专营精制棉织品，包括各灯家用亚麻制品，行销中东。 与贵公司向有业务联系，互利互作。贵公司纺织部亦十分了解有关业务合作之情况。 盼望能成为贵公司独家代理，促销在巴林市场的货品。 上述建议，烦请早日赐复，以便进一步联系合作。 此致 敬礼&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;拒绝对方担任独家代理
Thank you for your letter of 1 September suggesting that we grant you a sole agency for our household linens. I regret to say that, at this stage, such an arrangement would breather premature. We would, however, be willing to engage in a trial collaboration with you company to see how the arrangement works. It would be necessary for you to test the market for our products at you end. You would also have to build up a much larger turnover to justify a sole agency. We enclose price lists covering all the products you are interested in and look forward to hearing from you soon.9月1日有关建议担任家用亚麻制品独家代理的来信收悉。谨致衷心谢意。目前时机尚未成熟，不能应允该安排深感抱歉。 然而，本公司乐意与贵公司先试行合作，为今后合作打下基础。为证明担任独家代理的能力，贵公司宜上述货品作市场调查，研究是否可扩大现有之营业额。奉上该货品之报价单，敬希查照。专此候复。 此致 敬礼&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;同意对方担任独家代理
Thank you for your letter of 12 April proposing a sole agency for our office machines. We have examined our long and, I must say, mutually beneficial collaboration. We would be very pleased to entrust you with the sole agency for Bahrain. From our records, we are pleased to note that you have two service engineers who took training courses at our Milan factory .the sole agency will naturally be contingent on you maintaining qualified after sales staff. We have drawn up a draft agreement that is enclosed. Please examine the detailed terms and conditions and let us know whether they meet with your approval. On a personal note, I must say that I am delighted that we are probably going to strengthen our relationship. I have very pleasant memories of my last visit to Bahrain when you entertained me so delightfully .I look forward to reciprocating on your next visit to Milan. My very best wishes to you and your wife. 4月12日建议担任为公室器具之独家代理来信已经收悉。 过去双方合作皆互利互助，能获您的眷顾作我公司于巴林的独家代理，殊感荣幸。 据知您公司两服务技师曾到我公司米兰工厂受训。相信您公司在取得代理权后，仍会继续注重合格售后服务人员的训练。现随信附上协议草稿， 请查实各项条款 ，惠复是盼。 能加强业务，我亦感到欣喜，前次到访巴林，蒙盛情款待，不胜感激。祈盼您莅临米兰时，容我一尽地主之谊。 此致 敬礼&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;借引荐建立业务关系
At the beginning of this month , I attended the Harrogate toy fair. While there, I had an interesting conversation with Mr. Douglas Gage of Edutoys plc about selecting an agency for our teaching aids. Douglas described your dynamic sales force and innovative approach to marketing. He attributed his own company’s success to your excellent distribution network that has served him for several years. We need an organization like yours to launch our products in the UK. Our teaching aids cover the whole field of primary education in all subjects .Our patented ‘Matrix’ math apparatus is particularly successful. You may have reservations about American teaching aids suiting your market. This is not a problem since we have complete range of British English versions. I enclose an illustrated catalogue of our British English editions for your information. Please let me have your reactions to the material. I shall be in London during the first two weeks of October. Perhaps we could arrange a meeting to discuss our proposal.
本用初参观哈洛加特玩具交易会时有幸与教育玩具股份有限公司的道格拉斯•盖齐先生一谈，提及本公司正物色代理人推广教学器材一事。 盖齐先生赞扬贵公司积极推广产品，不断推出新的推销方法，并把其公司的成就归于贵公司完善的经销网络。贵公司的经验，正能替本公司在英国经销产品。 本公司生产初级教育各学科的教育器村、专利产品梅特里克教学器材更傲视同侪。 除美国教学器材外，亦备有全套英式英语版教材，适合当地市场，贵公司无需忧虑切合市场需求。 现附上配有插图的英式英语版教材目录，盼抽空细阅，并赐知宝贵意见。本人拟于10月头两星期前往伦敦，未知能否安排会面，就以上建议作一详谈? 此致 敬礼&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;与过去有贸易往来的公司联系
We understand from our trade contacts that your company has reestablished itself in Beirut and is once again trading successfully in your region. We would like to extend our congratulations and offer our very best wishes for your continued success. Before the war in Lebanon, our companies were involved in a large volume of trade in our textiles. We see from our records that you were among our best tem customers. We very much hope that we can resume our mutually beneficial relationship now that peace has returned to Lebanon. Since we last traded, our lines have changed beyond recognition. While they reflect current European taste in fabrics, some of our designs are specifically targeted at the Middle Eastern market. As an initial step, I enclose our illustrated catalogue for your perusal. Should you wish to receive samples for closer inspection, we will be very happy to forward them. We look forward to hearing from you. 从同行中获悉贵公司贝鲁特复业，生意发展迅速。得闻喜讯，不胜欢欣。谨祝业务蒸蒸日上。 黎巴嫩战事发生前双方曾有多宗纺织品交易；贵公司更是本公司十大客户之一。现今战事平息，亟盼能重展双方互惠的业务联系。 自上次合作至令，产品款式变化极大。除了有迎合欧洲人口味的款式这外，亦有专门为中东市场而设计的产品。现奉上配有插图的商品目录供 初步参考。职需查看样本，还望赐知。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;确认约会
I would like to confirm our appointment to discuss the possibility of merging our distribution networks. I am excited of the prospect of expanding our trade. As agreed, we will meet of our office in Bond Street at 9.30a.m.on Monday 20 March. I have scheduled the whole day for the meeting. If for any reason you are unable to attend, please phone me so that we can make alternative arrangements. Please let me know if you would like our office to arrange hotel accommodation. I look forward with great pleasure to our meeting. 承蒙拨冗讲讨论合并双方销售网，以扩大贸易发展范围，深感兴奋。现特修函确定会议日程。 谨于3月20日星期一在邦德街办公室候教，请贵公司代表于当日早上9时莅临指导。若因故未能抽空出席，烦请致电告知，以便另行安排会晤。 未知是否需代为安排旅馆膳宿?请尽早赐知，以便早作准备，款待贵客。 谨此预祝会谈成功。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;感谢客户订货
Gillette-burns Co. 322 Greenwood street Cleveland 5,Ohio Gentlemen: Thank you for your order No.464 of 20 September. The models you selected from our showroom went out today under my personal supervision. The package is being airfreight to you on Swissair. The relevant documentation is enclosed enjoyed meeting you and hopes that this order represents the beginning of a long and prosperous relationship between our companies. The next time you visit us, please let me know in advance so that I can arrange a lunch for you with our directors. Sincerely yours
谢谢9月20日第464号定单。今天我已新自监督发送您自展览室挑选的产品。该产品随附有关文件经瑞士航空公司运送。 很荣幸与你会面，衷心希望是次定单能加强双方的关系。下次到访前，烦请赐知，俾能安排与本公司董事共进午餐。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;向长期客户推销新产品
I enclose an illustrated supplement tour catalogue. It covers the latest designs, which are now available from stock. We are most gratified that you have, for several yeas. Include a selection of our products in your mail-order catalogues. The resulting sales have been very steady. We believe that you will find our new designs most attractive. They should get a very good reception in your market. Once you have had time to study the supplement, please let us know if you would like to take the matter further. We would be very happy to send samples to you for closer inspection. For your information, we are planning a range of classical English dinner services that should do well in the North American market. We will keep you informed on our progress and look forward to hearing from you. 随函寄奉配有插图的商品目录附页，介绍最新设计的产品。贵公司的邮购目录多年来收录本公司产品，产品销售成绩理想，特此致以深切谢意。最新设计的产品巧夺天工，定能吸引顾客选购。烦请参阅上述附页，需查看样本，请赐复，本公司乐意效劳。 本公司现正设计一系列款式古典的英国餐具，适合北美市场需求。如感兴趣，亦请赐知。 愿进一步加强联系，并候复音。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;为商贸指南兜揽广告
Thank you for your business. You are currently represented in our directory. This is the only directory of its kind, which reaches all companies in the building and construction industry in the UK. Advertising in our directory was a wise move on your part. We are currently compiling a new edition of the directory which will be published in April 1995.The new edition will be expanded to include major manufacturers of plumbing equipment in the European Community. For proper coverage in the directory, you ought to appear in more than one category. If you do opt for a multiple listing, you will be able to buy space in additional categories at half price. You can be assured that the new edition will be on the desks of all the major decision makers in the building and hardware trades. Please complete the enclosed form and return it with the appropriate fee. Thanks again for your business. 衷心感谢惠顾。贵公司商号已刊登在本公司的商贸指南中。该指南乃唯一覆盖英国全部建筑公司的刊物，在此刊登广告确是明智之举。 现下筹备1998年4月版 的贸易批南，新版会罗列欧洲贡同体的主要铅管业制造商。为达到出色的宣传效果，贵公司宜考虑在不同类别刊登广告。如蒙惠顾，除首个广告外，其余类别的广告将可获半价优惠。 该指南将分送给所有建筑公司和五金器具公司主管。烦表填妥随附表格，连同广告费用一并寄回。 专此盼候佳音。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;请求客户作推荐人
Thank you for your letter of 2 November. We are delighted to hear that you are to please with the refurbishment of your hotel. As your know .in our line of work, we depend on good, reports about our projects to win further business. Our clients always shop around and look for references before committing themselves. With your permission, we would like to use your hotel as a reference when we discuss similar refurbishments in the hotel industry. Would you agree to our suggesting that future clients should call you? It would also be most helpful if we could occasionally bring a client to look at your hotel. We would, of course, stay overnight at least. I’ll call you next week to hear your reaction. Thanks again for you kind words.从11月2日的来函得悉阁下对贵饭店的整修感到满意，此消息对本公司实是一鼓励。 设计行业重视声誉，客人在选择设计公司时必然会有所比较。如蒙允许，本公司欲请贵饭店作推荐人，证明有关整修的质素。未知可否让其他客户来电垂询? 此外，如获允准间或联同客户前来参观贵饭店整修，定必有莫大帮助。当然，本公司会预订房间，至少留宿一晚。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;通知客户价格调整
We enclose our new catalogue and price list. The revised prices will apply from 1 April 1997. You will see that there have been number of changes in our product range. A number of improved models have been introduced. Out range of washing machines has been completely revamped. Many popular lines, however, have been retained unchanged. You will be aware that inflation is affecting industry as a whole .Ws have been affected like everyone else and some price increases have been unavoidable. We have not, however, increased our prices across the board, In many cases, there is a small price increase, but in others, none at all. We can assure you that the quality of our consumer durables has been maintained at a high standard and that our service will continue to be first class. We look forward to receiving your orders. 谨谢上新的商品目录和价格表。修订价格定于1997年4月1日起生效。产品系列有一大革新，增加了不少改良的型号，扒出一系列新款的洗衣机，但许多款的开动号仍保持不变。通货膨胀影响整个工业连带令货品价格上涨。虽然如此，本公司并未全面提升价格，调整幅度亦不大。 本公司坚守一贯信念，务求出产优质之耐用消费品，迎合顾客的需要。 谢谢贵公司多年惠顾，盼继续合作。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;说明价格调整原因
I enclose our new price list, which will come into effect, from the end of this month. You will see that we have increased our prices on most models. We have, however, refrained from doing so on some models of which we hold large stocks. We feel we should explain why we have increased our prices. We are paying 10% more for our raw materials than we were paying last year. Some of our subcontractors have risen there by as much as 15%. As you know, we take great pride in our machines and are jealous of the reputation for quality and dependability that we have achieved over the last 40 years. We will not compromise that reputation because of rising costs. We hope, therefore decided to raise the price of some of our machines. We hope you will understand our position and look forward to your orders. 现谨附上本公司新价格表，新价格将于本月底生效。除了存货充裕的商品外，其余大部分货品均已调升价格。是次调整原因是原材料价格升幅上涨10%，一些承包商的价格调升到15%。 过去40年，本公司生产的机器品质优良、性能可靠。今为确保产品质量，唯有稍为调整价格。上述情况，还望考虑。愿能与贵公司保持紧密合作。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;回复感谢信
We greatly appreciate your letter describing the assistance you received in solving your air-conditioning problems. We are now in our fifty-year of operation, and we receive many letters like your indicating a high level of customer satisfaction with our installation. We are pleased that our technical staff assisted you so capably. We would like you to know that it you need to contact us at any time in the future. Our engineers will be equally responsive to your request for assistance. If we can be of service to you again, please let us know. Thank you again for your very kind letter. 承蒙来信赞扬本公司提供的空调维修工程服务，欣喜不已。五年前开业至今，屡获客户来函嘉奖，本公司荣幸之至。欣悉贵公司识技术人员的服务，他日苛有任何需要，亦请与本公司联络，本公司定当提供优秀技师，竭诚效劳。在此谨再衷心感谢贵公司的赞赏，并请继续保持联络。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;请客户征询其它公司
Thank you for your enquiry of 5 May concerning silk blouses. We regret to say that we do not manufacture clothing to your own designs to the highest European standards: Swan Textiles corporation The industrial zone Shako. We supply the factor with all their silk materials. I enclose a swatch of our stock materials for your examination. Should you desire any of these samples made up into finished products, we can supply the swan factory with them. We hope that this will be of help to you and wish you every success in your business dealings谢谢5月5月日来函查询关于纡绸罩衫的事宜。 本公司只生产纡绸布料，供应纺织品批发商和制造厂家，并没有制造成衣，因而未能接受贵公司订货，谨致万分歉意然而，本公司乐意推荐本地一家生产优质男装的工厂，相信可按贵公司设计的款式制造符合欧洲最高标准的服装：蛇口工业区天鹅纺织品公司。 该厂的丝绸布料全由本公司供应，随函了什样本以供查阅，如贵公司认为适合，本公司乐意负责供应所需布料。愿上资料对贵公司有所帮助。 谨祝生意兴隆，事事顺达。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;改善服务
Thank you for your letter of 26 January. I apologize for the delivery problems you had with us last month. I have had a meeting with our production and shipping managers to work out a better system for handling your account .We know we made a mistake on your last order. Although we have replaced it for you, we want to make sure it does not happen again. We have devised the enclosed checklist to use for each of your future order. It includes your firm’s particular specifications, packing requirements and marking instructions. I believe can service your company better and help you operations run more smoothly with this safeguard. Please contact us if there are any additional points you would like us to include.感谢1月26日来信。对上月贵公司更换所需货品，唯恐类似事件再发生，本公司生产、运输和出口部经理已商议制订更有效方法处理贵公司事务，并为此特别设计清单。 随信奉上该清单，供贵公司今后订货之用。当中包括特殊规格、包装要求和樗说明等栏目，相信此举有助本公司提供更佳服务，促进双方合作。如欲增设任何栏目于该清单上，恳求惠示。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;拒绝客户的要求
Thank you for your enquiry of 25 August. We are always pleased to hear from a valued customer. I regret to say that we cannot agree to your request for technical information regarding our software security systems. The fact is, that most of our competitors also keep such information private and confidential. I sincerely hope that this does not inconvenience you in any way. If there is any other way in which we can help. Do not hesitate to contact us again.8月25日信收悉，谨此致谢。 来信要求本公司提供有关软件保密系统的技术资料，但鉴于同行向来视该等资料为机密文件，本公司亦不便透露，尚祈见谅。我真诚地希望这样不会对贵公司造成不便。如需本公司协助其他事宜，欢迎随时赐顾垂询。 祝业务蒸蒸日上!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;应付难办的客户
We have been doing business together for a long time and we value our relationship of late, we have not been able to provide the kind of service we both want. The problem is that your purchasing department is changing orders after they have been placed. This has led to confusion and frustration for both of our companies. In several instances, you have returned goods that were originally ordered. To solve the problem, I propose that on receipt of an order, our sales staff contact you to verify it. If you decide on any changes, we will amend the order and fax you a copy so that you can check it. I trust this system will cut down on delays and errors, and allow our operations to run smoothly. 承蒙多年惠顾，本公司感激万分。然近来合作出现问题，令服务水准未能符合对方要求，本公司为此提忧不已。 贵公司采部发出定单后，再三更改内容；更有甚者，屡次退回订购之货品，导致了双方公司工作中的混乱和困惑。为避免问题日趋严重，特此在接到定单后，由本公司销售人员与贵公司复核。若需作出改支，本公司把定单修改后电传副本，供贵公司查核。 盼望上述办法经受减少延误，促进双方业务发展。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;祝贺新公司成立
It has just come to our attention that you have lately opened your new European headquarters in Brussels. Congratulations on your bold venture. As you know, our companies have had a long business association in the UK. We look forward to collaborating with you in your European venture. Please let us know if we can be of any assistance to you. We will be delighted to help. We wish you the very best of luck and a prosperous future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;修改信用证
Dear Mr. Jones:
We have received your L/C No.121/99 issued by the Yemen Bank for Reconstruction &amp;amp; Development for the amount of $19,720 covering 1,600 dozen Men’s Shirts. After reviewing the L/C, we find that transshipment and partial shipment are not allowed.
As direct steamers to your port are difficult to find, we have to ship via Hong Kong more often than not. As to partial shipment, it would be our mutual benefit because we could ship immediately whatever we have on hand instead waiting for the whole lot to be completed.
We, therefore, are writing this afternoon, asking you to amend the L/C to read: “TRANSSHIPMENT AND PARTIALSHIPMENT ALLOWED”
We shall be glad if you see to it that amendment is cabled without any delay, as our goods have been packed ready for shipment for quite some time.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;延期信用证的期限
Dear Mr. Jones:
We thank you for your L/C for the captioned goods. We are sorry that owing to some delay on the part of our suppliers at the point of origin, we are not able to get the goods ready before the end of this month. As a result, we sent you a cable yesterday reading: L/C1415 PLSCABLE EXTENSION SHIPMENT VALIDITY 15/31 MAY RESPECTIVELY LETFOLLOWS
It is expected that the consignment will be ready for shipment in the early part of May and we are arranging to ship it on s/s “Fanyang” sailing from Dalian on or about 10th May.
We are looking forward to receiving your cable extension of the above L/C thus enabling us to effect shipment of the goods in question.
We thank you for your cooperation.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;拒绝对方做独家代理商的要求
Dear Mr. Jones:
Thank you for your letter of 15th September.
As we are now only at the get-acquainted stage, we feel it is too early to take into consideration the matter of sole agency. In our opinion, it would be better for both of us to try out a period of cooperation to see how things go. Also, it would be necessary for you to test the marketability of our products at your end and to continue your efforts in building a larger turnover to justify the sole agency arrangement.
We enclose our latest pricelist covering all the products we handle within the framework of your specialized lines.
We look forward to hearing from you.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;指定对方为独家代理商
Dear Mr. Jones:
We have received your letter of the 15th and are impressed with the proposal you make. We are pleased to tell you that we have decided to entrust you with the sole agency for our Embroideries in the territory of Sweden.
The Agency Agreement has been drawn up for a duration of one year, automatically renewable on expiration for a similar period unless a written notice is given to the contrary. Enclosed you will find a copy of the draft. Please go over the provisions and advise us whether they meet with your approval.
We shall do all in our power to assist you in establishing a mutually beneficial trade.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;处理对货损的投诉
Dear Mr. Jones:
We have received your letter of 18th July, informing us that the sewing machines we shipped to you arrived in a damaged condition on account of imperfectness of our packing.
Upon receipt of your letter, we have given this matter our immediate attention. We have studied your surveyor’s report very carefully.
We are convinced that the present damage was due to extraordinary circumstances under which they were transported to you. We are therefore not responsible for the damage; but as we do not think that it would be fair to have you bear the loss alone, we suggest that the loss be divided between both of us, to which we hope you will agree.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;处理对货物品质的投诉
Dear Mr. Jones:
We very much regret to learn form your letter of 2nd March that you are not satisfied with the dress materials supplied to your order No.9578
From what you say it seems possible that some mistakes has been made in our selection of the materials meant for you and we are arranging for our Mr. Yang to call on you later this week to compare the materials supplied with the samples form which your ordered them.
If it is found that our selection faulty, then you can most certainly rely on us to replace the materials. In any case, we are willing to take the materials back and, if we can not supply what you want, to cancel your order, though do this reluctantly since we have no wish to lose your custom.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;主动跟新买家建立联系
Dear Mr. Jones:
We understand from your information posted on Alibaba.com that you are in the market for textiles. We would like to take this opportunity to introduce our company and products, with the hope that we may work with Bright Ideas Imports in the future.
We are a joint venture specializing in the manufacture and export of textiles. We have enclosed our catalog, which introduces our company in detail and covers the main products we supply at present. You may also visit our online company introduction at Http://www.广告 which includes our latest product line.
Should any of these items be of interest to you, please let us know. We will be happy to give you a quotation upon receipt of your detailed requirements.
We look forward to receiving your enquires soon.
Sincerely,
John Roberts&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;对新买家要求建立业务联系的回复
Dear Mr. Jones:
We have received your letter of 9th April showing your interest in our complete product information.
Our product lines mainly include high quality textile products. To give you a general idea of the various kinds of textiles now available for export, we have enclosed a catalogue and a price list. You may also visit our online company introduction at Http://www.广告 which includes our latest product line.
We look forward to your specific enquiries and hope to have the opportunity to work together with you in the future.
Sincerely,.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;向老客户介绍公司新的产品信息
Dear Mr. Jones:
We have refreshed our online catalog at http://www.广告, and now it covers the latest new products, which are now available from stock.
We believe that you will find some attractive additions to our product line. Once you have had time to study the supplement, please let us know if you would like to take the matter further. We would be very happy to send samples to you for close inspection.
We will keep you informed on our progress and look forward to hearing from you.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;回复对某个产品的查询
Dear Mr. Jones:
Thank you for your inquiry of 16 March. We are pleased to hear that you are interested in our product “toaster”.
We’ve enclosed the photo and detailed information of the product for your reference:
Product: toaster
Specification: xxxxxxxxxxxxxxx
Package: 1pcs/box
Price: 10usd/pcs
Payment: L/C
For purchase quantities over 1,000pcs of individual items we would allow you a discount of 1%. Payment is to be made by irrevocable L.C at sight.
We look forward to receiving your first order.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;无法提供对方查询中所要求的产品时
Dear Mr. Jones:
Thank you for your enquiry of 12 March cate 9 cable.
We appreciate your efforts in marketing our products and regret very much that we are unable to supply the desired goods due to excessive demand.
We would, however, like to take this opportunity to offer the following material as a close substitute:
Cate 5, US$__ per meter FOB Shanghai, including your commission 2%.
Please visit our catalog at http://www.xxxxxxxxx.com for more information on this item. If you find the product acceptable, please email us as soon as possible.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;查询对方公司的产品
Dear Sir or Madam:
We know that you are exporters of textile fabrics. We would like you to send us details of your various ranges, including colors and prices, and also samples of the different qualities of material used.
We are volume dealers in textiles and believe there is a promising market in our area for moderately priced goods of this kind mentioned.
When quoting, please state your terms of payment and discount you would allow on purchases of quantities of not less than 1000 meters of individual items. Prices quoted should include insurance and freight to San Francisco.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;几种报盘
(a.)
Dear Mr. Jones:
We thank you for your email enquiry for both groundnuts and Walnutmeat CNF Copenhagen dated February, 21.
In reply, we offer firm, subject to your reply reaching us on or before February 26 for 250 metric tons of groundnuts, handpicked, shelled and ungraded at RMB2000 net per metric ton CNF Copenhagen and any other European Main Ports. Shipment to be made within two months after receipt of your order payment by L/C payable by sight draft.
Please note that we have quoted our most favorable price and are unable to entertain any counter offer.
As you are aware that there has lately been a large demand for the above commodities. Such growing demand will likely result in increased prices. However you can secure these prices if you send us an immediate reply.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(b.)
Dear Mr. Jones:
We thank you for your letter dated April 8 inquiring about our leather handbags. As requested, we take pleasure in offering you, subject to our final confirmation, 300 dozen deerskin handbags style No.MS190 at $124.00 per dozen CIF Hamburg. Shipment will be effected within 20 days after receipt of the relevant L/C issued by your first class bank in our favor upon signing Sales Contract.
We are manufacturing various kinds of leather purses and waist belts for exportation, and enclosed a brochure of products for your reference. We hope some of them meet your taste and needs.
If we can be of any further help, please feel free to let us know. Customers’ inquiries are always meet with our careful attention.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(c.)
Re: SWC Sugar
Dear Sirs,
We are in receipt of your letter of July 17, 2002 asking us to offer 10,000 metric tons of the subject sugar for shipment to Japan and appreciate very much your interest in our product.
To comply with your request, we are offering you the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Commodity: Qingdao Superior White Crystal Sugar.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Packing: To be packed in new gunny bag of 100kgs. each.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Quantity: Ten thousand (10000) metric tons.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Price: US dollars one hundred and five (US$105.00) per metric ton, Fob Qingdao.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Payment: 100% by irrevocable and confirmed letter of credit to be opened in our favor through A1 bank in Qingdao and to be drawn at sight.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Shipment: Three or four weeks after receipt of letter of credit by the first available boat sailing to Yokohama direct.
Please note that we do not have much ready stock on hand. Therefore, it is important that, in order to enable us to effect early shipment, your letter of credit should be opened in time if our price meets with your approval.
We are awaiting your reply.
Sincerely,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;作为对方供应商，认为对方压价太低&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Mr. Jones:
We confirm having received your telex No.LT/531 of May 17, asking us to make a 10% reduction in our price for Men’s Shirts. Much to our regret, we are unable to comply with your request because we have given you the lowest possible price. We can assure you that the price quoted reflects the high quality of the products.
We still hope to have the opportunity to work with you and any further enquiry will receive our prompt attention.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;作为买家，认为对方报价太高
Dear Mr. Jones,
We acknowledge receipt of both your offer of May 6 and the samples of Men’s Shirts, and thank you for these.
While appreciating the good quality of your shirts, we find your price is rather too high for the market we wish to supply.
We have also to point out that the Men’s Shirts are available in our market from several European manufacturers, all of them are at prices from 10% to 15% below the price you quoted.
Such being the case, we have to ask you to consider if you can make reduction in your price, say 10%. As our order would be worth around US$50,000, you may think it worthwhile to make a concession.
We are looking forward to your reply,
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;要求对方开立信用证
Dear Mr. Jones:
With reference to the 4,000 dozen shirts under our Sales Confirmation No.SX260, we wish to draw your attention to the fact that the date of delivery is approaching but up to the present we have not received the covering L/C. Please do you utmost to expedite its establishment so that we may execute the order within the prescribed time.
In order to avoid subsequent amendments, please see to it that the L/C stipulations are in exact accordance with the terms of the contract.
We look forward to receiving your favorable response at an early date.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;因对方未能如期信用证而交涉
Dear Mr. Jones:
With reference to our Sales Confirmation No.825 dated August 10, 2002, we regret to say that your letter of credit has not yet reached us up to the time of writing. This has caused us much inconvenience as we have already made preparations for shipment according to the stipulations of the said Sales Confirmation.
You must be aware that the terms and conditions of a contract once signed should be strictly observed, failure to abide by them will mean violation of contract. If you refer to our Sales Confirmation, you will see the clause reading:
“The Buyer shall establish the covering Letter of Credit before 30th August, 2002, failing which the Seller reserves the right to rescind the contract without further notice.”
The goods you ordered have been ready for quite some time and the demand of late has been so great that we find it hard to keep them for you any longer. However, in consideration of our friendly business relations, we are prepared to wait for your L/C, which must reach us not later than October 5, 2002. If we again fail to receive your L/C in time, we shall cancel our Sales Confirmation and ask you to refund to us the storage charges we have paid on your behalf.
Your cooperation in this respect will be appreciated.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;修改信用证
Dear Mr. Jones:
We have received your L/C No.121/99 issued by the Yemen Bank for Reconstruction &amp;amp; Development for the amount of $19,720 covering 1,600 dozen Men’s Shirts. After reviewing the L/C, we find that transshipment and partial shipment are not allowed.
As direct steamers to your port are difficult to find, we have to ship via Hong Kong more often than not. As to partial shipment, it would be our mutual benefit because we could ship immediately whatever we have on hand instead waiting for the whole lot to be completed.
We, therefore, are writing this afternoon, asking you to amend the L/C to read: “TRANSSHIPMENT AND PARTIALSHIPMENT ALLOWED”
We shall be glad if you see to it that amendment is cabled without any delay, as our goods have been packed ready for shipment for quite some time.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;延期信用证的期限
Dear Mr. Jones:
We thank you for your L/C for the captioned goods. We are sorry that owing to some delay on the part of our suppliers at the point of origin, we are not able to get the goods ready before the end of this month. As a result, we sent you a cable yesterday reading: L/C1415 PLSCABLE EXTENSION SHIPMENT VALIDITY 15/31 MAY RESPECTIVELY LETFOLLOWS
It is expected that the consignment will be ready for shipment in the early part of May and we are arranging to ship it on s/s “Fanyang” sailing from Dalian on or about 10th May.
We are looking forward to receiving your cable extension of the above L/C thus enabling us to effect shipment of the goods in question.
We thank you for your cooperation.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;拒绝对方做独家代理商的要求
Dear Mr. Jones:
Thank you for your letter of 15th September.
As we are now only at the get-acquainted stage, we feel it is too early to take into consideration the matter of sole agency. In our opinion, it would be better for both of us to try out a period of cooperation to see how things go. Also, it would be necessary for you to test the marketability of our products at your end and to continue your efforts in building a larger turnover to justify the sole agency arrangement.
We enclose our latest pricelist covering all the products we handle within the framework of your specialized lines.
We look forward to hearing from you.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;指定对方为独家代理商
Dear Mr. Jones:
We have received your letter of the 15th and are impressed with the proposal you make. We are pleased to tell you that we have decided to entrust you with the sole agency for our Embroideries in the territory of Sweden.
The Agency Agreement has been drawn up for a duration of one year, automatically renewable on expiration for a similar period unless a written notice is given to the contrary. Enclosed you will find a copy of the draft. Please go over the provisions and advise us whether they meet with your approval.
We shall do all in our power to assist you in establishing a mutually beneficial trade.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;处理对货损的投诉
Dear Mr. Jones:
We have received your letter of 18th July, informing us that the sewing machines we shipped to you arrived in a damaged condition on account of imperfectness of our packing.
Upon receipt of your letter, we have given this matter our immediate attention. We have studied your surveyor’s report very carefully.
We are convinced that the present damage was due to extraordinary circumstances under which they were transported to you. We are therefore not responsible for the damage; but as we do not think that it would be fair to have you bear the loss alone, we suggest that the loss be divided between both of us, to which we hope you will agree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;放假通知邮件
Hi ***:
How about business recently?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am writing to tell you that our factory and office will be temporarily closed from 1st Oct to 7th Oct, for the National Day holiday, and we will be back in office on 8th Oct.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any enquiries, pls send me email, I will check it during that time. Sorry for any inconvenience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have a nice day,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;处理对货物品质的投诉
Dear Mr. Jones:
We very much regret to learn form your letter of 2nd March that you are not satisfied with the dress materials supplied to your order No.9578
From what you say it seems possible that some mistakes has been made in our selection of the materials meant for you and we are arranging for our Mr. Yang to call on you later this week to compare the materials supplied with the samples form which your ordered them.
If it is found that our selection faulty, then you can most certainly rely on us to replace the materials. In any case, we are willing to take the materials back and, if we can not supply what you want, to cancel your order, though do this reluctantly since we have no wish to lose your custom.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;圣诞节祝福邮件模版
Christmas Best Wishes to Customers
Dear xxx
The holiday season offers us a special opportunity to extend our personal thanks to our friends， and our very best wishes for the future.! O% l- u0 P6 p% |7 Z
And so it is that we now gather together and wish to you a very Merry Christmas and a Happy New Year. We consider you a good friend and extend our wishes for good health and good cheer.
It is people like you who make being in business such a pleasure all year long. Our business is a source of pride to us， and with customers like you， we find going to work each day a rewarding experience.
We tip our glasses to you. Thanks again for a wonderful year.
Yours sincerely,
××××
×××× China&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;范文二：
Dear Mr. FOB,
We would like to extend our warm wishes for the upcoming holiday season and would like to wish you and your family a Merry Christmas and a prosperous New Year. We also would like to take this opportunity to say thank you for your business and support over the years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our office will be officially closed the following times during the holiday period: from Monday 24th December to Monday 2nd January&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our support team will still answer emails through the Holidays, however, please be patient as our response time may be a little slower than usual.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May you travel safely over this busy festive season and come back refreshed for a successful 2008.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Best Wishes,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1.没成交的客户
To:   &lt;br /&gt;
From:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear ,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Merry Christmas and happy New Year!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Christmas and New Year holiday is coming near once again. We would like to extend our warm wishes for the upcoming holiday season and would like to wish you and your family a Merry Christmas and a prosperous New Year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May your New Year be filled with special moment, warmth, peace and happiness, the joy of covered ones near, and wishing you all the joys of Christmas and a year of happiness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s my honor to contact with you before, and my duty is to give you our best products and excellent service.Hope the next year is a prosperous and harvest year for both of us !Last but not least, once you have any inquiry about *****（products）in the following days, hope you could feel free to contact with us, which is much appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yours sincerely&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;已成交的客户
My dearest&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happy Christmas and new year!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many thanks for your contiguous supports in the past years, we wish both business snowballing in the coming years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May your New Year be filled with special moment, warmth, peace and happiness, the joy of covered ones near, and wishing you all the joys of Christmas and a year of happiness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last but not least, once you have any inquiry about products in the following days, hope you could feel free to contact with us, which is much appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yours sincerely&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;温馨提示
为了帮助大家提高外贸邮件送达率和转化率，本人温馨提示，在发送外贸邮件的时候，需要注意一下几点：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;非常简洁明了的标题&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;语言要简洁，多用短句, 长句一定要分拆为短句，哪怕多写几句&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;语气要委婉 ，不要用 YOU SHOULD KNOW, YOU SHOULD, YOU MUST这类，也不要说什么YOUR ORDER IS TOO SMALL，换种语气，会非常好&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;多用被动语态       真正的老美写邮件是很少 用 WE, I 之类的第一人称，通常都是用被动 比如，I WILL INFORM YOU TRACKING NO. SOON.  老美会写，THE TRACKING NO. WILL BE SUPPLIED SOON&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;段落之间的逻辑关系一定要清晰&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;有选择的情况下，不要用陈述句，要用 选择句型   比如外贸人常用的 our price is XXX for 2000 pcs but it is XXX for 3000 pcs Do you want to buy 2000 pcs or 3000 pcs?
      另外，就是在要提出解决办法的时候，一定要用 1, 2 , 3…. 简洁明白的说出来，然后让客户选择，或者提问  What is your idea or solution?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;注意中式英语，很多都是习惯问题，我们自己看的很明白，很清楚，但是，老外就很难看懂。&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;如果发送量比较大，建议采用第三方专业邮件营销服务提供商来发送。 我这里推荐一家公司的软件。Comm100邮件营销软件，我一个月前开始使用他们的产品的。总的来说，他们的软件，操作蛮方便的，不需要注册大量邮箱，发送量也没有限制；送达率也比较高，我几次下来，都能达到92%以上；另外本人最喜欢的功能是统计功能比较强大，可以清楚的知道谁收到邮件，谁点击了邮件中链接。他们的网站是：http://www.comm100.cn/emailmarketingnewsletter/
有兴趣的童鞋，可以去试用一下。&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;注意邮件里面的字体一直，颜色等问题  一般老外都用 ARIAL 这个字体。&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;称呼  有的人喜欢用 hi my brother, hi boss, hi manager, dear  sir 等等，这些不要所有的客户都用一种，要根据客户的反应来称呼，通常要客户保持一致，或者要根据客户的年龄，性格等等去区分，不能简单的就将所有的客户用同一个称呼。 有的客户是BOSS, 有的是MANAGER, 有的只是一般采购代表。在国外公司的邮件都是有监控系统的。在没有搞清对方身份或者爱好前，乱称呼是有风险的。&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;注意多用详细的数据，比如多少数量，多少箱，多重，多少钱，PI号码，多少天数 等等，这类信息都是非常重要。&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;多用感谢的话，多用问候，结尾不要一成不变地是 HAVE A NICE DAY BEST REGARDS
可以这样写：
祝你今天过得非常愉快
祝你有一个美好的一天
周末愉快
祝你有个好心情
祝贺你今天撞大运
……&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;针对客户的邮件多问客户一些问题，多用 WHAT DO YOU THINK?  WHAT IS YOUR IDEA?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;多跟客户套近乎          黏住一个客户是非常重要的事情，所以怎样跟客户做成朋友就非常关键了。这里，外贸行业有一个说法：不会跟客户谈“恋爱”的业务一定做不成一个好业务。所以，做外贸，常常也是在跟 自己的产品谈恋爱，跟客户谈恋爱。&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;节日的问候，圣诞节一定要给客户发电子贺卡。平时其他一些重大节日也要问候客户。&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;发生重大事件跟客户交流想法，比如 冰岛火山，地震，海啸，也要及时问候当地的客户。&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;我们自己公司的放假通知一定要提前传达给客户。&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;用心写好每一封邮件         这点是最难做到的，很多人都是忽视了这点。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="English" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">外贸邮件英文模版</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english-trading-email/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="外贸邮件英文模版" /><published>2020-01-29T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2020-01-29T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english-trading-email</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english-trading-email/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.magvision.com/uploads/allimg/190304/1-1Z30416331U05.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- more --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;开发信模板(一)
Company Name:
Mailing Add:
Tel.:
Fax.:
Email:
Web.:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kind Attn.: Mr. Jack Wey– General Manager (hope I would be the GM one day)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Subject: XXXXX Cooperation/&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Mr. Jack Wey&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[Your company] is the main [your product] manufacturer in China since 1968, our major clients are[those have very good reputation and renown companies in the field that have direct or indirect biz with your company, i.e. IBM, SONY .. ].&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We believe that you can rely on us as we provide you quite satisfactory service and products with best quality at most competitive price in the world. We are very happy if you do not hesitate to send us any of your inquiries and we will always give satisfactory services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Products: (product range)
Standards: (product design standard, if any)
Service: (product applicable field, function)
Size: (don’t fuckingly tell your client you don’t know)
Etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Certificates: (certificates that your company got)
Annual Sales Turnover: ( just list some number here,)
Staff No.staff no of your company, if your company is big, if not, omit this point)
Cover of Land list some number here)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking forward to hearing from you at your convenience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks &amp;amp; best regards,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.S. I am attaching our product catalogue/scope of service for your future reference in my following email to you, please kindly check.
( please don’t send your product catalogue in the email, you are telling him here is showing your respect to him that you are sending good info to him,but not spam, therefore, you better send another email to your client with your product catalogue. Your client will check it if your products are of him/her interest)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;YOUR NAME
POSITION
DEPARTMENT
COMPANY NAME
ADD
TEL
MOBILE
FAX
EMAIL
WEB&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear all, I am jack wey, this above mentioned email for marketing is only one sample to your general potential clients, it would be revised accordingly to different clients.
Kindly be informed that email marketing is mainly depending on your SET title, therefore pls try to improve TO SET THE TITLE OF YOUR EMAIL.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;（开发信的成功与否，跟开发信内容的大少无关，关键是你怎么把涉及到客户每一个利益、兴趣都说到，能连起来，他都会像继续看下去，要不我们还看电视连续剧干嘛？)
邮件开发成功与否与以下几个方面有关（个人认为）：（按主次顺序）&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;邮件标题（要是我，邮件标题一看就知道是推销的，I am sorry, please fuck off and stay in my trash box）&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;邮件内容是否吸引/对客户是否有效，有利可图；客户是否感兴趣.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;所联系的人的职位和权利（Pls send to the RIGHT PERSON）&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;发信人日后沟通技巧，plus&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;others&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;以上的开发信只是针对任意一家公司，如果要想开发信更成功，你就得研究或者了解一下这个公司的情况再发。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;有的开发信中，并不能把所有东西都一一列出来，所以一天发个100封的开发信的人，一天很难记下前天发给谁了，日后很难去跟踪，也不知道自己以前说了什么，如果是这样，最好做个记录；邮件已发出3天之内，马上再发一封邮件跟踪，过2如没有回复，再发一封了解，第三封邮件刚发后30分钟，马上给个电话。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;记住，成功的开发信，一般要有电话跟踪才能比较有效果，当然有幸运的人，或是客户也正好有询价，有货采购才会直接跟你联系，所以为什么要日后电话沟通的原因。现在一般一个客户一天能收到很多信，你只有电话过去了，说明你请况，他才知道你是谁，什么公司，下次在电话的时候，他会说“oh, Jack? Jack wey from China,XXX company? Oh, how are you? …..”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;开发信模板(二)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Mr. JACK,
Thank you for your e-mail &amp;amp; I do appreciate the content.（讲得是我开发信的内容）
I do not have any hesitation to start business with your esteemed company.对我公司感兴趣
Thus I ask you kindly to arrange courier me full set of all your catalogs in one binder along with copies of all your certificates , end user approvals ,..etc. 需要一些文件进一步合作&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, I would like to hear from you in details about your previous operation in middle east area .
Do you have agent,distributer,..etc?想成为我们代理分销商&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Best Regards
XXXXXXXXXXXXX&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;现在说说我开发信主要的信息：
标题： Mr. XXX + 他公司的名称 （点名道姓和公司，一目了然）
内容：
MOrning！ Mr. XXXXXX&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is Jack, Sales Manager from a well established PRODUCT manufacturer in China. Hope I reach the right person at the right time to talk about PRODUCT cooperation and strategies for your company?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did a little bit research on your company and I’m sure you would be continuously looking at opportunities to expand your product supplying scope/services and make it as the brand to own your company reputation in the PRODUCT market and increase your market return with your constant efforts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can fulfill any of your business needs and maximize your business profits compared with lots of PRODUCT manufacturers as we are newly launching DDDD brand PRODUCT in international market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our business reference includes:
? 20 years appointed OEM for EU,USA PRODUCT manufacturers
? Approvals from …….(主要客户，最好是国际同行知名企业)…
? 70%~80% products for international application
(for more details, please contact us) 这个地方用黄色文字背景，突出公司优势&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the GM of 客户公司名称 , it is your responsibility to find a sustainable and trustworthy business partner relationship and ensure a promising company future. 我的公司 is interested in cooperating with you to uncover the PRODUCT demand of 客户市场 market from now on. As you have experiences in PROCUT, it would be easier to seize the opportunity to win great PRODUCT demand in 客户市场。
（这里很明显的标示你的合作意图和对客户公司的了解及所联系人的职责所在，没有人会反对你强调他的职责和利益）&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hope to have your excited feedback TODAY.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks ®ards,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JACK
24 hours available for you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;请求建立商业关系
Rogers Chemical Supply Co. 10E.22Street Omaha8, Neb Gentlemen: We have obtained your name and address from Aristo Shoes, Milan, and we are writing to enquire whether you would be willing to establish business relations with us. We have been importers of shoes for many years. At present, We are interested in extending our, range and would appreciate your catalogues and quotations. If your prices were competitive we would expect to transact a significant volume of business. We look forward to your early reply.Very truly yours 自米兰职权里斯托鞋类公司取得贵公司和地址，特此修函，祈能发展关系。多年来，本公司经营鞋类进口生意，现欲扩展业务范围。盼能惠赐商品目录和报价表。 如价格公道，本公司必大额订购。 烦请早日赐复。 此致&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2.回复对方建立商业关系的请求
Thank your for your letter of the 16th of this month. We shall be glad to enter into business relations with your company. In compliance with your request, we are sending you, under separate cover, our latest catalogue and price list covering our export range. Payment should be made by irrevocable and confirmed letter of credit. Should you wish to place an order, please telex or fax us. 本月16日收到有关商务关系的来函，不胜欣喜。谨遵要求另函奉上最新之出口商品目录和报价单。款项烦请以不可撤销保兑之信用状支付。如欲订货，请电传或传真为盼。 此致 敬礼&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;请求担任独家代理
We would like to inform you that we act on a sole agency basis for a number of manufacturers. We specialize in finished cotton goods for the Middle eastern market: Our activities cover all types of household linen. Until now, we have been working with your textiles department and our collaboration has proved to be mutually beneficial. Please refer to them for any information regarding our company. We are very interested in an exclusive arrangement with your factory for the promotion of your products in Bahrain. We look forward to your early reply. `本公司担任多家厂家的独家代理，专营精制棉织品，包括各灯家用亚麻制品，行销中东。 与贵公司向有业务联系，互利互作。贵公司纺织部亦十分了解有关业务合作之情况。 盼望能成为贵公司独家代理，促销在巴林市场的货品。 上述建议，烦请早日赐复，以便进一步联系合作。 此致 敬礼&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;拒绝对方担任独家代理
Thank you for your letter of 1 September suggesting that we grant you a sole agency for our household linens. I regret to say that, at this stage, such an arrangement would breather premature. We would, however, be willing to engage in a trial collaboration with you company to see how the arrangement works. It would be necessary for you to test the market for our products at you end. You would also have to build up a much larger turnover to justify a sole agency. We enclose price lists covering all the products you are interested in and look forward to hearing from you soon.9月1日有关建议担任家用亚麻制品独家代理的来信收悉。谨致衷心谢意。目前时机尚未成熟，不能应允该安排深感抱歉。 然而，本公司乐意与贵公司先试行合作，为今后合作打下基础。为证明担任独家代理的能力，贵公司宜上述货品作市场调查，研究是否可扩大现有之营业额。奉上该货品之报价单，敬希查照。专此候复。 此致 敬礼&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;同意对方担任独家代理
Thank you for your letter of 12 April proposing a sole agency for our office machines. We have examined our long and, I must say, mutually beneficial collaboration. We would be very pleased to entrust you with the sole agency for Bahrain. From our records, we are pleased to note that you have two service engineers who took training courses at our Milan factory .the sole agency will naturally be contingent on you maintaining qualified after sales staff. We have drawn up a draft agreement that is enclosed. Please examine the detailed terms and conditions and let us know whether they meet with your approval. On a personal note, I must say that I am delighted that we are probably going to strengthen our relationship. I have very pleasant memories of my last visit to Bahrain when you entertained me so delightfully .I look forward to reciprocating on your next visit to Milan. My very best wishes to you and your wife. 4月12日建议担任为公室器具之独家代理来信已经收悉。 过去双方合作皆互利互助，能获您的眷顾作我公司于巴林的独家代理，殊感荣幸。 据知您公司两服务技师曾到我公司米兰工厂受训。相信您公司在取得代理权后，仍会继续注重合格售后服务人员的训练。现随信附上协议草稿， 请查实各项条款 ，惠复是盼。 能加强业务，我亦感到欣喜，前次到访巴林，蒙盛情款待，不胜感激。祈盼您莅临米兰时，容我一尽地主之谊。 此致 敬礼&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;借引荐建立业务关系
At the beginning of this month , I attended the Harrogate toy fair. While there, I had an interesting conversation with Mr. Douglas Gage of Edutoys plc about selecting an agency for our teaching aids. Douglas described your dynamic sales force and innovative approach to marketing. He attributed his own company’s success to your excellent distribution network that has served him for several years. We need an organization like yours to launch our products in the UK. Our teaching aids cover the whole field of primary education in all subjects .Our patented ‘Matrix’ math apparatus is particularly successful. You may have reservations about American teaching aids suiting your market. This is not a problem since we have complete range of British English versions. I enclose an illustrated catalogue of our British English editions for your information. Please let me have your reactions to the material. I shall be in London during the first two weeks of October. Perhaps we could arrange a meeting to discuss our proposal.
本用初参观哈洛加特玩具交易会时有幸与教育玩具股份有限公司的道格拉斯•盖齐先生一谈，提及本公司正物色代理人推广教学器材一事。 盖齐先生赞扬贵公司积极推广产品，不断推出新的推销方法，并把其公司的成就归于贵公司完善的经销网络。贵公司的经验，正能替本公司在英国经销产品。 本公司生产初级教育各学科的教育器村、专利产品梅特里克教学器材更傲视同侪。 除美国教学器材外，亦备有全套英式英语版教材，适合当地市场，贵公司无需忧虑切合市场需求。 现附上配有插图的英式英语版教材目录，盼抽空细阅，并赐知宝贵意见。本人拟于10月头两星期前往伦敦，未知能否安排会面，就以上建议作一详谈? 此致 敬礼&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;与过去有贸易往来的公司联系
We understand from our trade contacts that your company has reestablished itself in Beirut and is once again trading successfully in your region. We would like to extend our congratulations and offer our very best wishes for your continued success. Before the war in Lebanon, our companies were involved in a large volume of trade in our textiles. We see from our records that you were among our best tem customers. We very much hope that we can resume our mutually beneficial relationship now that peace has returned to Lebanon. Since we last traded, our lines have changed beyond recognition. While they reflect current European taste in fabrics, some of our designs are specifically targeted at the Middle Eastern market. As an initial step, I enclose our illustrated catalogue for your perusal. Should you wish to receive samples for closer inspection, we will be very happy to forward them. We look forward to hearing from you. 从同行中获悉贵公司贝鲁特复业，生意发展迅速。得闻喜讯，不胜欢欣。谨祝业务蒸蒸日上。 黎巴嫩战事发生前双方曾有多宗纺织品交易；贵公司更是本公司十大客户之一。现今战事平息，亟盼能重展双方互惠的业务联系。 自上次合作至令，产品款式变化极大。除了有迎合欧洲人口味的款式这外，亦有专门为中东市场而设计的产品。现奉上配有插图的商品目录供 初步参考。职需查看样本，还望赐知。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;确认约会
I would like to confirm our appointment to discuss the possibility of merging our distribution networks. I am excited of the prospect of expanding our trade. As agreed, we will meet of our office in Bond Street at 9.30a.m.on Monday 20 March. I have scheduled the whole day for the meeting. If for any reason you are unable to attend, please phone me so that we can make alternative arrangements. Please let me know if you would like our office to arrange hotel accommodation. I look forward with great pleasure to our meeting. 承蒙拨冗讲讨论合并双方销售网，以扩大贸易发展范围，深感兴奋。现特修函确定会议日程。 谨于3月20日星期一在邦德街办公室候教，请贵公司代表于当日早上9时莅临指导。若因故未能抽空出席，烦请致电告知，以便另行安排会晤。 未知是否需代为安排旅馆膳宿?请尽早赐知，以便早作准备，款待贵客。 谨此预祝会谈成功。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;感谢客户订货
Gillette-burns Co. 322 Greenwood street Cleveland 5,Ohio Gentlemen: Thank you for your order No.464 of 20 September. The models you selected from our showroom went out today under my personal supervision. The package is being airfreight to you on Swissair. The relevant documentation is enclosed enjoyed meeting you and hopes that this order represents the beginning of a long and prosperous relationship between our companies. The next time you visit us, please let me know in advance so that I can arrange a lunch for you with our directors. Sincerely yours
谢谢9月20日第464号定单。今天我已新自监督发送您自展览室挑选的产品。该产品随附有关文件经瑞士航空公司运送。 很荣幸与你会面，衷心希望是次定单能加强双方的关系。下次到访前，烦请赐知，俾能安排与本公司董事共进午餐。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;向长期客户推销新产品
I enclose an illustrated supplement tour catalogue. It covers the latest designs, which are now available from stock. We are most gratified that you have, for several yeas. Include a selection of our products in your mail-order catalogues. The resulting sales have been very steady. We believe that you will find our new designs most attractive. They should get a very good reception in your market. Once you have had time to study the supplement, please let us know if you would like to take the matter further. We would be very happy to send samples to you for closer inspection. For your information, we are planning a range of classical English dinner services that should do well in the North American market. We will keep you informed on our progress and look forward to hearing from you. 随函寄奉配有插图的商品目录附页，介绍最新设计的产品。贵公司的邮购目录多年来收录本公司产品，产品销售成绩理想，特此致以深切谢意。最新设计的产品巧夺天工，定能吸引顾客选购。烦请参阅上述附页，需查看样本，请赐复，本公司乐意效劳。 本公司现正设计一系列款式古典的英国餐具，适合北美市场需求。如感兴趣，亦请赐知。 愿进一步加强联系，并候复音。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;为商贸指南兜揽广告
Thank you for your business. You are currently represented in our directory. This is the only directory of its kind, which reaches all companies in the building and construction industry in the UK. Advertising in our directory was a wise move on your part. We are currently compiling a new edition of the directory which will be published in April 1995.The new edition will be expanded to include major manufacturers of plumbing equipment in the European Community. For proper coverage in the directory, you ought to appear in more than one category. If you do opt for a multiple listing, you will be able to buy space in additional categories at half price. You can be assured that the new edition will be on the desks of all the major decision makers in the building and hardware trades. Please complete the enclosed form and return it with the appropriate fee. Thanks again for your business. 衷心感谢惠顾。贵公司商号已刊登在本公司的商贸指南中。该指南乃唯一覆盖英国全部建筑公司的刊物，在此刊登广告确是明智之举。 现下筹备1998年4月版 的贸易批南，新版会罗列欧洲贡同体的主要铅管业制造商。为达到出色的宣传效果，贵公司宜考虑在不同类别刊登广告。如蒙惠顾，除首个广告外，其余类别的广告将可获半价优惠。 该指南将分送给所有建筑公司和五金器具公司主管。烦表填妥随附表格，连同广告费用一并寄回。 专此盼候佳音。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;请求客户作推荐人
Thank you for your letter of 2 November. We are delighted to hear that you are to please with the refurbishment of your hotel. As your know .in our line of work, we depend on good, reports about our projects to win further business. Our clients always shop around and look for references before committing themselves. With your permission, we would like to use your hotel as a reference when we discuss similar refurbishments in the hotel industry. Would you agree to our suggesting that future clients should call you? It would also be most helpful if we could occasionally bring a client to look at your hotel. We would, of course, stay overnight at least. I’ll call you next week to hear your reaction. Thanks again for you kind words.从11月2日的来函得悉阁下对贵饭店的整修感到满意，此消息对本公司实是一鼓励。 设计行业重视声誉，客人在选择设计公司时必然会有所比较。如蒙允许，本公司欲请贵饭店作推荐人，证明有关整修的质素。未知可否让其他客户来电垂询? 此外，如获允准间或联同客户前来参观贵饭店整修，定必有莫大帮助。当然，本公司会预订房间，至少留宿一晚。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;通知客户价格调整
We enclose our new catalogue and price list. The revised prices will apply from 1 April 1997. You will see that there have been number of changes in our product range. A number of improved models have been introduced. Out range of washing machines has been completely revamped. Many popular lines, however, have been retained unchanged. You will be aware that inflation is affecting industry as a whole .Ws have been affected like everyone else and some price increases have been unavoidable. We have not, however, increased our prices across the board, In many cases, there is a small price increase, but in others, none at all. We can assure you that the quality of our consumer durables has been maintained at a high standard and that our service will continue to be first class. We look forward to receiving your orders. 谨谢上新的商品目录和价格表。修订价格定于1997年4月1日起生效。产品系列有一大革新，增加了不少改良的型号，扒出一系列新款的洗衣机，但许多款的开动号仍保持不变。通货膨胀影响整个工业连带令货品价格上涨。虽然如此，本公司并未全面提升价格，调整幅度亦不大。 本公司坚守一贯信念，务求出产优质之耐用消费品，迎合顾客的需要。 谢谢贵公司多年惠顾，盼继续合作。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;说明价格调整原因
I enclose our new price list, which will come into effect, from the end of this month. You will see that we have increased our prices on most models. We have, however, refrained from doing so on some models of which we hold large stocks. We feel we should explain why we have increased our prices. We are paying 10% more for our raw materials than we were paying last year. Some of our subcontractors have risen there by as much as 15%. As you know, we take great pride in our machines and are jealous of the reputation for quality and dependability that we have achieved over the last 40 years. We will not compromise that reputation because of rising costs. We hope, therefore decided to raise the price of some of our machines. We hope you will understand our position and look forward to your orders. 现谨附上本公司新价格表，新价格将于本月底生效。除了存货充裕的商品外，其余大部分货品均已调升价格。是次调整原因是原材料价格升幅上涨10%，一些承包商的价格调升到15%。 过去40年，本公司生产的机器品质优良、性能可靠。今为确保产品质量，唯有稍为调整价格。上述情况，还望考虑。愿能与贵公司保持紧密合作。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;回复感谢信
We greatly appreciate your letter describing the assistance you received in solving your air-conditioning problems. We are now in our fifty-year of operation, and we receive many letters like your indicating a high level of customer satisfaction with our installation. We are pleased that our technical staff assisted you so capably. We would like you to know that it you need to contact us at any time in the future. Our engineers will be equally responsive to your request for assistance. If we can be of service to you again, please let us know. Thank you again for your very kind letter. 承蒙来信赞扬本公司提供的空调维修工程服务，欣喜不已。五年前开业至今，屡获客户来函嘉奖，本公司荣幸之至。欣悉贵公司识技术人员的服务，他日苛有任何需要，亦请与本公司联络，本公司定当提供优秀技师，竭诚效劳。在此谨再衷心感谢贵公司的赞赏，并请继续保持联络。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;请客户征询其它公司
Thank you for your enquiry of 5 May concerning silk blouses. We regret to say that we do not manufacture clothing to your own designs to the highest European standards: Swan Textiles corporation The industrial zone Shako. We supply the factor with all their silk materials. I enclose a swatch of our stock materials for your examination. Should you desire any of these samples made up into finished products, we can supply the swan factory with them. We hope that this will be of help to you and wish you every success in your business dealings谢谢5月5月日来函查询关于纡绸罩衫的事宜。 本公司只生产纡绸布料，供应纺织品批发商和制造厂家，并没有制造成衣，因而未能接受贵公司订货，谨致万分歉意然而，本公司乐意推荐本地一家生产优质男装的工厂，相信可按贵公司设计的款式制造符合欧洲最高标准的服装：蛇口工业区天鹅纺织品公司。 该厂的丝绸布料全由本公司供应，随函了什样本以供查阅，如贵公司认为适合，本公司乐意负责供应所需布料。愿上资料对贵公司有所帮助。 谨祝生意兴隆，事事顺达。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;改善服务
Thank you for your letter of 26 January. I apologize for the delivery problems you had with us last month. I have had a meeting with our production and shipping managers to work out a better system for handling your account .We know we made a mistake on your last order. Although we have replaced it for you, we want to make sure it does not happen again. We have devised the enclosed checklist to use for each of your future order. It includes your firm’s particular specifications, packing requirements and marking instructions. I believe can service your company better and help you operations run more smoothly with this safeguard. Please contact us if there are any additional points you would like us to include.感谢1月26日来信。对上月贵公司更换所需货品，唯恐类似事件再发生，本公司生产、运输和出口部经理已商议制订更有效方法处理贵公司事务，并为此特别设计清单。 随信奉上该清单，供贵公司今后订货之用。当中包括特殊规格、包装要求和樗说明等栏目，相信此举有助本公司提供更佳服务，促进双方合作。如欲增设任何栏目于该清单上，恳求惠示。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;拒绝客户的要求
Thank you for your enquiry of 25 August. We are always pleased to hear from a valued customer. I regret to say that we cannot agree to your request for technical information regarding our software security systems. The fact is, that most of our competitors also keep such information private and confidential. I sincerely hope that this does not inconvenience you in any way. If there is any other way in which we can help. Do not hesitate to contact us again.8月25日信收悉，谨此致谢。 来信要求本公司提供有关软件保密系统的技术资料，但鉴于同行向来视该等资料为机密文件，本公司亦不便透露，尚祈见谅。我真诚地希望这样不会对贵公司造成不便。如需本公司协助其他事宜，欢迎随时赐顾垂询。 祝业务蒸蒸日上!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;应付难办的客户
We have been doing business together for a long time and we value our relationship of late, we have not been able to provide the kind of service we both want. The problem is that your purchasing department is changing orders after they have been placed. This has led to confusion and frustration for both of our companies. In several instances, you have returned goods that were originally ordered. To solve the problem, I propose that on receipt of an order, our sales staff contact you to verify it. If you decide on any changes, we will amend the order and fax you a copy so that you can check it. I trust this system will cut down on delays and errors, and allow our operations to run smoothly. 承蒙多年惠顾，本公司感激万分。然近来合作出现问题，令服务水准未能符合对方要求，本公司为此提忧不已。 贵公司采部发出定单后，再三更改内容；更有甚者，屡次退回订购之货品，导致了双方公司工作中的混乱和困惑。为避免问题日趋严重，特此在接到定单后，由本公司销售人员与贵公司复核。若需作出改支，本公司把定单修改后电传副本，供贵公司查核。 盼望上述办法经受减少延误，促进双方业务发展。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;祝贺新公司成立
It has just come to our attention that you have lately opened your new European headquarters in Brussels. Congratulations on your bold venture. As you know, our companies have had a long business association in the UK. We look forward to collaborating with you in your European venture. Please let us know if we can be of any assistance to you. We will be delighted to help. We wish you the very best of luck and a prosperous future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;修改信用证
Dear Mr. Jones:
We have received your L/C No.121/99 issued by the Yemen Bank for Reconstruction &amp;amp; Development for the amount of $19,720 covering 1,600 dozen Men’s Shirts. After reviewing the L/C, we find that transshipment and partial shipment are not allowed.
As direct steamers to your port are difficult to find, we have to ship via Hong Kong more often than not. As to partial shipment, it would be our mutual benefit because we could ship immediately whatever we have on hand instead waiting for the whole lot to be completed.
We, therefore, are writing this afternoon, asking you to amend the L/C to read: “TRANSSHIPMENT AND PARTIALSHIPMENT ALLOWED”
We shall be glad if you see to it that amendment is cabled without any delay, as our goods have been packed ready for shipment for quite some time.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;延期信用证的期限
Dear Mr. Jones:
We thank you for your L/C for the captioned goods. We are sorry that owing to some delay on the part of our suppliers at the point of origin, we are not able to get the goods ready before the end of this month. As a result, we sent you a cable yesterday reading: L/C1415 PLSCABLE EXTENSION SHIPMENT VALIDITY 15/31 MAY RESPECTIVELY LETFOLLOWS
It is expected that the consignment will be ready for shipment in the early part of May and we are arranging to ship it on s/s “Fanyang” sailing from Dalian on or about 10th May.
We are looking forward to receiving your cable extension of the above L/C thus enabling us to effect shipment of the goods in question.
We thank you for your cooperation.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;拒绝对方做独家代理商的要求
Dear Mr. Jones:
Thank you for your letter of 15th September.
As we are now only at the get-acquainted stage, we feel it is too early to take into consideration the matter of sole agency. In our opinion, it would be better for both of us to try out a period of cooperation to see how things go. Also, it would be necessary for you to test the marketability of our products at your end and to continue your efforts in building a larger turnover to justify the sole agency arrangement.
We enclose our latest pricelist covering all the products we handle within the framework of your specialized lines.
We look forward to hearing from you.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;指定对方为独家代理商
Dear Mr. Jones:
We have received your letter of the 15th and are impressed with the proposal you make. We are pleased to tell you that we have decided to entrust you with the sole agency for our Embroideries in the territory of Sweden.
The Agency Agreement has been drawn up for a duration of one year, automatically renewable on expiration for a similar period unless a written notice is given to the contrary. Enclosed you will find a copy of the draft. Please go over the provisions and advise us whether they meet with your approval.
We shall do all in our power to assist you in establishing a mutually beneficial trade.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;处理对货损的投诉
Dear Mr. Jones:
We have received your letter of 18th July, informing us that the sewing machines we shipped to you arrived in a damaged condition on account of imperfectness of our packing.
Upon receipt of your letter, we have given this matter our immediate attention. We have studied your surveyor’s report very carefully.
We are convinced that the present damage was due to extraordinary circumstances under which they were transported to you. We are therefore not responsible for the damage; but as we do not think that it would be fair to have you bear the loss alone, we suggest that the loss be divided between both of us, to which we hope you will agree.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;处理对货物品质的投诉
Dear Mr. Jones:
We very much regret to learn form your letter of 2nd March that you are not satisfied with the dress materials supplied to your order No.9578
From what you say it seems possible that some mistakes has been made in our selection of the materials meant for you and we are arranging for our Mr. Yang to call on you later this week to compare the materials supplied with the samples form which your ordered them.
If it is found that our selection faulty, then you can most certainly rely on us to replace the materials. In any case, we are willing to take the materials back and, if we can not supply what you want, to cancel your order, though do this reluctantly since we have no wish to lose your custom.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;主动跟新买家建立联系
Dear Mr. Jones:
We understand from your information posted on Alibaba.com that you are in the market for textiles. We would like to take this opportunity to introduce our company and products, with the hope that we may work with Bright Ideas Imports in the future.
We are a joint venture specializing in the manufacture and export of textiles. We have enclosed our catalog, which introduces our company in detail and covers the main products we supply at present. You may also visit our online company introduction at Http://www.广告 which includes our latest product line.
Should any of these items be of interest to you, please let us know. We will be happy to give you a quotation upon receipt of your detailed requirements.
We look forward to receiving your enquires soon.
Sincerely,
John Roberts&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;对新买家要求建立业务联系的回复
Dear Mr. Jones:
We have received your letter of 9th April showing your interest in our complete product information.
Our product lines mainly include high quality textile products. To give you a general idea of the various kinds of textiles now available for export, we have enclosed a catalogue and a price list. You may also visit our online company introduction at Http://www.广告 which includes our latest product line.
We look forward to your specific enquiries and hope to have the opportunity to work together with you in the future.
Sincerely,.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;向老客户介绍公司新的产品信息
Dear Mr. Jones:
We have refreshed our online catalog at http://www.广告, and now it covers the latest new products, which are now available from stock.
We believe that you will find some attractive additions to our product line. Once you have had time to study the supplement, please let us know if you would like to take the matter further. We would be very happy to send samples to you for close inspection.
We will keep you informed on our progress and look forward to hearing from you.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;回复对某个产品的查询
Dear Mr. Jones:
Thank you for your inquiry of 16 March. We are pleased to hear that you are interested in our product “toaster”.
We’ve enclosed the photo and detailed information of the product for your reference:
Product: toaster
Specification: xxxxxxxxxxxxxxx
Package: 1pcs/box
Price: 10usd/pcs
Payment: L/C
For purchase quantities over 1,000pcs of individual items we would allow you a discount of 1%. Payment is to be made by irrevocable L.C at sight.
We look forward to receiving your first order.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;无法提供对方查询中所要求的产品时
Dear Mr. Jones:
Thank you for your enquiry of 12 March cate 9 cable.
We appreciate your efforts in marketing our products and regret very much that we are unable to supply the desired goods due to excessive demand.
We would, however, like to take this opportunity to offer the following material as a close substitute:
Cate 5, US$__ per meter FOB Shanghai, including your commission 2%.
Please visit our catalog at http://www.xxxxxxxxx.com for more information on this item. If you find the product acceptable, please email us as soon as possible.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;查询对方公司的产品
Dear Sir or Madam:
We know that you are exporters of textile fabrics. We would like you to send us details of your various ranges, including colors and prices, and also samples of the different qualities of material used.
We are volume dealers in textiles and believe there is a promising market in our area for moderately priced goods of this kind mentioned.
When quoting, please state your terms of payment and discount you would allow on purchases of quantities of not less than 1000 meters of individual items. Prices quoted should include insurance and freight to San Francisco.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;几种报盘
(a.)
Dear Mr. Jones:
We thank you for your email enquiry for both groundnuts and Walnutmeat CNF Copenhagen dated February, 21.
In reply, we offer firm, subject to your reply reaching us on or before February 26 for 250 metric tons of groundnuts, handpicked, shelled and ungraded at RMB2000 net per metric ton CNF Copenhagen and any other European Main Ports. Shipment to be made within two months after receipt of your order payment by L/C payable by sight draft.
Please note that we have quoted our most favorable price and are unable to entertain any counter offer.
As you are aware that there has lately been a large demand for the above commodities. Such growing demand will likely result in increased prices. However you can secure these prices if you send us an immediate reply.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(b.)
Dear Mr. Jones:
We thank you for your letter dated April 8 inquiring about our leather handbags. As requested, we take pleasure in offering you, subject to our final confirmation, 300 dozen deerskin handbags style No.MS190 at $124.00 per dozen CIF Hamburg. Shipment will be effected within 20 days after receipt of the relevant L/C issued by your first class bank in our favor upon signing Sales Contract.
We are manufacturing various kinds of leather purses and waist belts for exportation, and enclosed a brochure of products for your reference. We hope some of them meet your taste and needs.
If we can be of any further help, please feel free to let us know. Customers’ inquiries are always meet with our careful attention.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(c.)
Re: SWC Sugar
Dear Sirs,
We are in receipt of your letter of July 17, 2002 asking us to offer 10,000 metric tons of the subject sugar for shipment to Japan and appreciate very much your interest in our product.
To comply with your request, we are offering you the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Commodity: Qingdao Superior White Crystal Sugar.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Packing: To be packed in new gunny bag of 100kgs. each.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Quantity: Ten thousand (10000) metric tons.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Price: US dollars one hundred and five (US$105.00) per metric ton, Fob Qingdao.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Payment: 100% by irrevocable and confirmed letter of credit to be opened in our favor through A1 bank in Qingdao and to be drawn at sight.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Shipment: Three or four weeks after receipt of letter of credit by the first available boat sailing to Yokohama direct.
Please note that we do not have much ready stock on hand. Therefore, it is important that, in order to enable us to effect early shipment, your letter of credit should be opened in time if our price meets with your approval.
We are awaiting your reply.
Sincerely,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;作为对方供应商，认为对方压价太低&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear Mr. Jones:
We confirm having received your telex No.LT/531 of May 17, asking us to make a 10% reduction in our price for Men’s Shirts. Much to our regret, we are unable to comply with your request because we have given you the lowest possible price. We can assure you that the price quoted reflects the high quality of the products.
We still hope to have the opportunity to work with you and any further enquiry will receive our prompt attention.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;作为买家，认为对方报价太高
Dear Mr. Jones,
We acknowledge receipt of both your offer of May 6 and the samples of Men’s Shirts, and thank you for these.
While appreciating the good quality of your shirts, we find your price is rather too high for the market we wish to supply.
We have also to point out that the Men’s Shirts are available in our market from several European manufacturers, all of them are at prices from 10% to 15% below the price you quoted.
Such being the case, we have to ask you to consider if you can make reduction in your price, say 10%. As our order would be worth around US$50,000, you may think it worthwhile to make a concession.
We are looking forward to your reply,
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;要求对方开立信用证
Dear Mr. Jones:
With reference to the 4,000 dozen shirts under our Sales Confirmation No.SX260, we wish to draw your attention to the fact that the date of delivery is approaching but up to the present we have not received the covering L/C. Please do you utmost to expedite its establishment so that we may execute the order within the prescribed time.
In order to avoid subsequent amendments, please see to it that the L/C stipulations are in exact accordance with the terms of the contract.
We look forward to receiving your favorable response at an early date.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;因对方未能如期信用证而交涉
Dear Mr. Jones:
With reference to our Sales Confirmation No.825 dated August 10, 2002, we regret to say that your letter of credit has not yet reached us up to the time of writing. This has caused us much inconvenience as we have already made preparations for shipment according to the stipulations of the said Sales Confirmation.
You must be aware that the terms and conditions of a contract once signed should be strictly observed, failure to abide by them will mean violation of contract. If you refer to our Sales Confirmation, you will see the clause reading:
“The Buyer shall establish the covering Letter of Credit before 30th August, 2002, failing which the Seller reserves the right to rescind the contract without further notice.”
The goods you ordered have been ready for quite some time and the demand of late has been so great that we find it hard to keep them for you any longer. However, in consideration of our friendly business relations, we are prepared to wait for your L/C, which must reach us not later than October 5, 2002. If we again fail to receive your L/C in time, we shall cancel our Sales Confirmation and ask you to refund to us the storage charges we have paid on your behalf.
Your cooperation in this respect will be appreciated.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;修改信用证
Dear Mr. Jones:
We have received your L/C No.121/99 issued by the Yemen Bank for Reconstruction &amp;amp; Development for the amount of $19,720 covering 1,600 dozen Men’s Shirts. After reviewing the L/C, we find that transshipment and partial shipment are not allowed.
As direct steamers to your port are difficult to find, we have to ship via Hong Kong more often than not. As to partial shipment, it would be our mutual benefit because we could ship immediately whatever we have on hand instead waiting for the whole lot to be completed.
We, therefore, are writing this afternoon, asking you to amend the L/C to read: “TRANSSHIPMENT AND PARTIALSHIPMENT ALLOWED”
We shall be glad if you see to it that amendment is cabled without any delay, as our goods have been packed ready for shipment for quite some time.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;延期信用证的期限
Dear Mr. Jones:
We thank you for your L/C for the captioned goods. We are sorry that owing to some delay on the part of our suppliers at the point of origin, we are not able to get the goods ready before the end of this month. As a result, we sent you a cable yesterday reading: L/C1415 PLSCABLE EXTENSION SHIPMENT VALIDITY 15/31 MAY RESPECTIVELY LETFOLLOWS
It is expected that the consignment will be ready for shipment in the early part of May and we are arranging to ship it on s/s “Fanyang” sailing from Dalian on or about 10th May.
We are looking forward to receiving your cable extension of the above L/C thus enabling us to effect shipment of the goods in question.
We thank you for your cooperation.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;拒绝对方做独家代理商的要求
Dear Mr. Jones:
Thank you for your letter of 15th September.
As we are now only at the get-acquainted stage, we feel it is too early to take into consideration the matter of sole agency. In our opinion, it would be better for both of us to try out a period of cooperation to see how things go. Also, it would be necessary for you to test the marketability of our products at your end and to continue your efforts in building a larger turnover to justify the sole agency arrangement.
We enclose our latest pricelist covering all the products we handle within the framework of your specialized lines.
We look forward to hearing from you.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;指定对方为独家代理商
Dear Mr. Jones:
We have received your letter of the 15th and are impressed with the proposal you make. We are pleased to tell you that we have decided to entrust you with the sole agency for our Embroideries in the territory of Sweden.
The Agency Agreement has been drawn up for a duration of one year, automatically renewable on expiration for a similar period unless a written notice is given to the contrary. Enclosed you will find a copy of the draft. Please go over the provisions and advise us whether they meet with your approval.
We shall do all in our power to assist you in establishing a mutually beneficial trade.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;处理对货损的投诉
Dear Mr. Jones:
We have received your letter of 18th July, informing us that the sewing machines we shipped to you arrived in a damaged condition on account of imperfectness of our packing.
Upon receipt of your letter, we have given this matter our immediate attention. We have studied your surveyor’s report very carefully.
We are convinced that the present damage was due to extraordinary circumstances under which they were transported to you. We are therefore not responsible for the damage; but as we do not think that it would be fair to have you bear the loss alone, we suggest that the loss be divided between both of us, to which we hope you will agree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;放假通知邮件
Hi ***:
How about business recently?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am writing to tell you that our factory and office will be temporarily closed from 1st Oct to 7th Oct, for the National Day holiday, and we will be back in office on 8th Oct.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any enquiries, pls send me email, I will check it during that time. Sorry for any inconvenience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have a nice day,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;处理对货物品质的投诉
Dear Mr. Jones:
We very much regret to learn form your letter of 2nd March that you are not satisfied with the dress materials supplied to your order No.9578
From what you say it seems possible that some mistakes has been made in our selection of the materials meant for you and we are arranging for our Mr. Yang to call on you later this week to compare the materials supplied with the samples form which your ordered them.
If it is found that our selection faulty, then you can most certainly rely on us to replace the materials. In any case, we are willing to take the materials back and, if we can not supply what you want, to cancel your order, though do this reluctantly since we have no wish to lose your custom.
Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;圣诞节祝福邮件模版
Christmas Best Wishes to Customers
Dear xxx
The holiday season offers us a special opportunity to extend our personal thanks to our friends， and our very best wishes for the future.! O% l- u0 P6 p% |7 Z
And so it is that we now gather together and wish to you a very Merry Christmas and a Happy New Year. We consider you a good friend and extend our wishes for good health and good cheer.
It is people like you who make being in business such a pleasure all year long. Our business is a source of pride to us， and with customers like you， we find going to work each day a rewarding experience.
We tip our glasses to you. Thanks again for a wonderful year.
Yours sincerely,
××××
×××× China&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;范文二：
Dear Mr. FOB,
We would like to extend our warm wishes for the upcoming holiday season and would like to wish you and your family a Merry Christmas and a prosperous New Year. We also would like to take this opportunity to say thank you for your business and support over the years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our office will be officially closed the following times during the holiday period: from Monday 24th December to Monday 2nd January&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our support team will still answer emails through the Holidays, however, please be patient as our response time may be a little slower than usual.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May you travel safely over this busy festive season and come back refreshed for a successful 2008.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Best Wishes,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1.没成交的客户
To:   &lt;br /&gt;
From:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dear ,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Merry Christmas and happy New Year!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Christmas and New Year holiday is coming near once again. We would like to extend our warm wishes for the upcoming holiday season and would like to wish you and your family a Merry Christmas and a prosperous New Year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May your New Year be filled with special moment, warmth, peace and happiness, the joy of covered ones near, and wishing you all the joys of Christmas and a year of happiness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s my honor to contact with you before, and my duty is to give you our best products and excellent service.Hope the next year is a prosperous and harvest year for both of us !Last but not least, once you have any inquiry about *****（products）in the following days, hope you could feel free to contact with us, which is much appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yours sincerely&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;已成交的客户
My dearest&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happy Christmas and new year!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many thanks for your contiguous supports in the past years, we wish both business snowballing in the coming years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May your New Year be filled with special moment, warmth, peace and happiness, the joy of covered ones near, and wishing you all the joys of Christmas and a year of happiness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last but not least, once you have any inquiry about products in the following days, hope you could feel free to contact with us, which is much appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yours sincerely&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;温馨提示
为了帮助大家提高外贸邮件送达率和转化率，本人温馨提示，在发送外贸邮件的时候，需要注意一下几点：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;非常简洁明了的标题&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;语言要简洁，多用短句, 长句一定要分拆为短句，哪怕多写几句&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;语气要委婉 ，不要用 YOU SHOULD KNOW, YOU SHOULD, YOU MUST这类，也不要说什么YOUR ORDER IS TOO SMALL，换种语气，会非常好&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;多用被动语态       真正的老美写邮件是很少 用 WE, I 之类的第一人称，通常都是用被动 比如，I WILL INFORM YOU TRACKING NO. SOON.  老美会写，THE TRACKING NO. WILL BE SUPPLIED SOON&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;段落之间的逻辑关系一定要清晰&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;有选择的情况下，不要用陈述句，要用 选择句型   比如外贸人常用的 our price is XXX for 2000 pcs but it is XXX for 3000 pcs Do you want to buy 2000 pcs or 3000 pcs?
      另外，就是在要提出解决办法的时候，一定要用 1, 2 , 3…. 简洁明白的说出来，然后让客户选择，或者提问  What is your idea or solution?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;注意中式英语，很多都是习惯问题，我们自己看的很明白，很清楚，但是，老外就很难看懂。&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;如果发送量比较大，建议采用第三方专业邮件营销服务提供商来发送。 我这里推荐一家公司的软件。Comm100邮件营销软件，我一个月前开始使用他们的产品的。总的来说，他们的软件，操作蛮方便的，不需要注册大量邮箱，发送量也没有限制；送达率也比较高，我几次下来，都能达到92%以上；另外本人最喜欢的功能是统计功能比较强大，可以清楚的知道谁收到邮件，谁点击了邮件中链接。他们的网站是：http://www.comm100.cn/emailmarketingnewsletter/
有兴趣的童鞋，可以去试用一下。&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;注意邮件里面的字体一直，颜色等问题  一般老外都用 ARIAL 这个字体。&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;称呼  有的人喜欢用 hi my brother, hi boss, hi manager, dear  sir 等等，这些不要所有的客户都用一种，要根据客户的反应来称呼，通常要客户保持一致，或者要根据客户的年龄，性格等等去区分，不能简单的就将所有的客户用同一个称呼。 有的客户是BOSS, 有的是MANAGER, 有的只是一般采购代表。在国外公司的邮件都是有监控系统的。在没有搞清对方身份或者爱好前，乱称呼是有风险的。&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;注意多用详细的数据，比如多少数量，多少箱，多重，多少钱，PI号码，多少天数 等等，这类信息都是非常重要。&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;多用感谢的话，多用问候，结尾不要一成不变地是 HAVE A NICE DAY BEST REGARDS
可以这样写：
祝你今天过得非常愉快
祝你有一个美好的一天
周末愉快
祝你有个好心情
祝贺你今天撞大运
……&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;针对客户的邮件多问客户一些问题，多用 WHAT DO YOU THINK?  WHAT IS YOUR IDEA?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;多跟客户套近乎          黏住一个客户是非常重要的事情，所以怎样跟客户做成朋友就非常关键了。这里，外贸行业有一个说法：不会跟客户谈“恋爱”的业务一定做不成一个好业务。所以，做外贸，常常也是在跟 自己的产品谈恋爱，跟客户谈恋爱。&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;节日的问候，圣诞节一定要给客户发电子贺卡。平时其他一些重大节日也要问候客户。&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;发生重大事件跟客户交流想法，比如 冰岛火山，地震，海啸，也要及时问候当地的客户。&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;我们自己公司的放假通知一定要提前传达给客户。&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;用心写好每一封邮件         这点是最难做到的，很多人都是忽视了这点。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="English" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">什么是Spring boot中的 bean</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/java-bean/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="什么是Spring boot中的 bean" /><published>2020-01-27T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2020-01-27T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/java-bean</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/java-bean/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://dzone.com/storage/temp/12766233-coffee-beans-photo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- more --&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;修改AndroidManifest.xml文件，添加渠道名称变量&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;div class=&quot;language-xml highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;         &lt;span class=&quot;c&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;!--value的值填写渠道名称，例如yingyongbao。这里设置动态渠道名称变量--&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
         &lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;meta-data&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;android:value=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;${UMENG_CHANNEL_VALUE}&quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;android:name=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;UMENG_CHANNEL&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;/&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;修改app的build.gradle文件，添加所需要的渠道&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;div class=&quot;language-java highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;     &lt;span class=&quot;cm&quot;&gt;/*配置渠道*/&lt;/span&gt;
     &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;productFlavors&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
         &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;yingyongbao&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
             &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;manifestPlaceholders&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nl&quot;&gt;UMENG_CHANNEL_VALUE:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;yingyongbao&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;]&lt;/span&gt;
         &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
         &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;wandoujia&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
             &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;manifestPlaceholders&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nl&quot;&gt;UMENG_CHANNEL_VALUE:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;wandoujia&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;]&lt;/span&gt;
         &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
         &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;xiaomi&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
             &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;manifestPlaceholders&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nl&quot;&gt;UMENG_CHANNEL_VALUE:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;xiaomi&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;]&lt;/span&gt;
         &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
     &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;如果遇到一下错误，可以参考google文档修改解决&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;div class=&quot;language-bash highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;     Error:All flavors must now belong to a named flavor dimension.
     The flavor &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;'flavor_name'&lt;/span&gt; is not assigned to a flavor dimension.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;在build.gradle文件的defaultConfig段落中添加&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;div class=&quot;language-java highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;     &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;flavorDimensions&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;versionCode&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.android.com/studio/build/build-variants?utm_source=android-studio#product-flavors&quot; title=&quot;Google's document&quot;&gt;参考链接1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnblogs.com/WUXIAOCHANG/p/10683942.html&quot; title=&quot;cnblogs's document&quot;&gt;参考链接2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jianshu.com/p/e4da2f477cd8&quot; title=&quot;jianshu's document&quot;&gt;参考链接3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Java" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">even, even if, even though 区别</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english-even-if-though/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="even, even if, even though 区别" /><published>2020-01-27T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2020-01-27T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english-even-if-though</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english-even-if-though/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.liberaldictionary.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/01/even.png&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- more --&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Even - 甚至&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Even if - 即使、纵然 （假设，可以用于虚拟语气）&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Even though - 即使、纵然 （真实场景）&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="English" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">21 more advanced alternative phrases of “I think …”</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english-I-think/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="21 more advanced alternative phrases of &quot;I think ...&quot;" /><published>2020-01-27T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2020-01-27T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english-I-think</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english-I-think/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://discoveryinaction.com.au/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/image-1.png&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- more --&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I’m not going to lie …&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;I’m not going to lie, I was pretty insulted to not be invited to my ex boyfriend’s wedding.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;in all honesty …&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;In all honesty, I had every right to be there.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;in my view …&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;In my view, I should’ve been invited so it was totally fair for me to turn up on the day.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;if you ask me …&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;If you ask me, the church service was wonderful, but it was a shame I had to stand at the back.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;as far as I can tell …&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;As far as I can tell, the bride wasn’t really expecting me.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;to my mind …&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;To my mind, she should’ve been happier to see me and reveive my support.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;as far as I’m concerned …&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;As far as I’m concerned, she totally overreacted and shouldn’t have cried.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;the way I see things/it …&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;The way I see things, I made the family photographs a lot more interesting.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;as I see things/it …&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;As I see it, they obviously didn’t take me into consideration when drawing up the seating plans.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;it seems to me that … the&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;It seems to me that everyone overreacted when I tried to sit at the top table.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I believe …&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;I believe that they should have just made space for me in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I would say …&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;I’d say that food was very good, but it was a shame I had to share with my neighbour.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I consider … to be …&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;I consider it to be very rude that I was forced to sit down when I stood up to make a speech.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;to me …&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;To me, no one knows my ex better than me so I should’v been able to tell all of our funny stories.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;from my point of view …&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;From my point of view, the first dance was cringe-worthy so I did everyone a favour by joining in.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;it is my view/belief that …&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;It is my view that the open bar made everything worse.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I reckon …&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;I reckon the sixth gin and tonic tipped me over the edge.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I honestly believe that …&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;I honestly believe that if I hadn’t started cutting the cake, no one would have.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;honestly speaking …&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Honestly speaking, I probably shouldn’t have thrown my slice at the bride.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I feel that …&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;I feel that my ex could have found a more welcoming bride with a better sense of humour.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;personally speaking …&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Personally speaking, calling the police was a bit OTT.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Notes:&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Over the top (OTT)&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;to an excessive or exaggerated degree&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="English" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Android 友盟多渠道打包</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/android-apk/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Android 友盟多渠道打包" /><published>2020-01-22T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2020-01-22T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/android-apk</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/android-apk/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.ritavpn.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2019/12/Best-APK-Download-Sites-for-2020.png&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- more --&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;修改AndroidManifest.xml文件，添加渠道名称变量&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;div class=&quot;language-xml highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;         &lt;span class=&quot;c&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;!--value的值填写渠道名称，例如yingyongbao。这里设置动态渠道名称变量--&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
         &lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;meta-data&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;android:value=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;${UMENG_CHANNEL_VALUE}&quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;android:name=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;UMENG_CHANNEL&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;/&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;修改app的build.gradle文件，添加所需要的渠道&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;div class=&quot;language-java highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;     &lt;span class=&quot;cm&quot;&gt;/*配置渠道*/&lt;/span&gt;
     &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;productFlavors&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
         &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;yingyongbao&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
             &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;manifestPlaceholders&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nl&quot;&gt;UMENG_CHANNEL_VALUE:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;yingyongbao&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;]&lt;/span&gt;
         &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
         &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;wandoujia&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
             &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;manifestPlaceholders&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nl&quot;&gt;UMENG_CHANNEL_VALUE:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;wandoujia&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;]&lt;/span&gt;
         &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
         &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;xiaomi&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
             &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;manifestPlaceholders&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nl&quot;&gt;UMENG_CHANNEL_VALUE:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;xiaomi&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;]&lt;/span&gt;
         &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
     &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;如果遇到一下错误，可以参考google文档修改解决&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;div class=&quot;language-bash highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;     Error:All flavors must now belong to a named flavor dimension.
     The flavor &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;'flavor_name'&lt;/span&gt; is not assigned to a flavor dimension.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;在build.gradle文件的defaultConfig段落中添加&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;div class=&quot;language-java highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;     &lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;flavorDimensions&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;versionCode&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.android.com/studio/build/build-variants?utm_source=android-studio#product-flavors&quot; title=&quot;Google's document&quot;&gt;参考链接1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnblogs.com/WUXIAOCHANG/p/10683942.html&quot; title=&quot;cnblogs's document&quot;&gt;参考链接2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jianshu.com/p/e4da2f477cd8&quot; title=&quot;jianshu's document&quot;&gt;参考链接3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Android" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">laugh, smile, siggle, grin, beam, sneer 区别</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english-laugh-smile-siggle-grin-beam-sneer/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="laugh, smile, siggle, grin, beam, sneer 区别" /><published>2020-01-22T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2020-01-22T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english-laugh-smile-siggle-grin-beam-sneer</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english-laugh-smile-siggle-grin-beam-sneer/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.beautiful-women-pedia.com/images/woman-smiling-text-photo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- more --&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;laugh : 最常用词，指因喜悦、愉快或轻视而出声的笑或大笑。&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;smile : 指面露微笑，侧重于无声。&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;siggle : 指发出咯咯的笑声，较多地用于女人或孩子。&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;grin : 指露齿而笑。&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;beam : 书面用词，指人因心情舒畅而发出的笑，即喜形于色地笑。&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;sneer : 指冷笑、嘲笑。&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;chuckle : 轻声笑&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;snicker : 忍笑&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;roar : 哄笑&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;simper : 假笑&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;cachinnate : 放声大笑&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="English" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Choose, select, pick, elect, prefer, opt 区别</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english-choose-select-pick-elect-opt-prefer/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Choose, select, pick, elect, prefer, opt 区别" /><published>2020-01-21T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2020-01-21T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english-choose-select-pick-elect-opt-prefer</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english-choose-select-pick-elect-opt-prefer/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://jacobspradlin.files.wordpress.com/2013/08/choosetech.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- more --&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;choose
 这是很平常的普通用词，侧重于根据个人的意愿和判断在众多的对象中进行选择，较为看重别选者的优点，但是这个词会强调在选择的过程中所下的决心。&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;普通用词，主要表达个人意愿和判断大多数人的选择&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;例如：&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;They will be able to choose their own leaders in democratic elections.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;The local shops have been marked in on this map so that people can choose a house in a suitable area.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;pick
 这个就是很常见的口语用词，大多数情况指的是从个人角度进行仔细的挑选，也含有任意的进行挑选，也就是不需要进行仔细的挑选或进行辨别。&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;口语用词，指从个人的一主观仔细挑选，比较随意的挑选&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;例如：&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Mr. Nowell had picked ten people to interview for six sales jobs in Dallas.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;If your proposed syntax picks one of them then you need to give me a syntax to pick the others.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;select
 在写作中用这个词应该是会比较多的，因为这是个书面用语，在使用的时候，有时是会具有庄严、正式的感情色彩，所强调的是在认真的考虑之后，从很多的人或者物里面精心选出最好的，最中意的。&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;书面用词，用于庄严、正式的场合，强调精选&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;例如：&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Voters are selecting candidates for both U.S. Senate seats and for 52 congressional seats.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;But within one data set you can view it in a number of different formats and select from a range of different variables.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;elect
 别看它比select少了个‘S’，但是这也是一个选择，这个一般指的是按照一定的规章或法律，在一定的范围里面，在有限的数量中，用投票等等的方式所进行的认真、慎重的选择。&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;指按一定的规章或法律，用投票等方式进行的认真、慎重的选择&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;例如：&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;The people of the Philippines have voted to elect a new president.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;In many cases we need also to take account of the responsibility of patients for their own health, and voters for the governments they elect.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;prefer
 这个选择说是选择，其实也可以说不是选择，其所强调的是因为个人的偏爱所做的选择，但是不一定会有选择的行动。&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;强调个人偏爱，但不一定有选择的行为。&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;例如：&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;I became a teacher because I preferred books and people to politics.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;She chose Spain, but personally I’d prefer to go to France.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;opt
 这个选择的范围是比较小的，一般都是指在几种可能性之间进行的选择。&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;多指在几种可能性之间进行选择。&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;例如：&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;After graduating she opted for a career in music.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Employees may opt out of the company’s pension plan.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;single
 这个选择算得上是精挑细选，强调的是从若干的人或者物中，很慎重的挑选出符合要求的人或者物。&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;例如：&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;He was singled out to succeed his uncle.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="English" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">apparatus, instrument, device, equipment, tool, implement, installation, appliance, facilities 区别</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english-apparatus-instrument-device-equipment-tool-implement-installation-appliance-facilities/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="apparatus, instrument, device, equipment, tool, implement, installation, appliance, facilities 区别" /><published>2020-01-10T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2020-01-10T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english-apparatus-instrument-device-equipment-tool-implement-installation-appliance-facilities</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english-apparatus-instrument-device-equipment-tool-implement-installation-appliance-facilities/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cookmankitchenequipments.files.wordpress.com/2015/09/commercial-kitchen-equipment-supplies-l-40da9a0c49163d9c.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- more --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;这些名词均有“仪器、设备、器械、器具”之意。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;apparatus:&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;既可指某种具体的由许多不同零件构成的复杂的仪器、装置或器械，又可指它们的总称。&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Firefighters needed breathing apparatus to enter the burning house.
消防队员需要呼吸器以便进入燃烧的大楼。&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;instrument:&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;通常指能使人们完成某一精确动作或测量的一种小型仪器，尤指电工仪表、测量装置，航海或航空用的控制装置。&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;a thin tube-like optical instrument
试管状的细长光学仪器&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;device:&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;多指为某一特殊用途或解决某一特定机械问题而设计或改装的精巧的仪器或装置。&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;“device” 通常指 “小巧的电子装置或设备”，比如 “移动设备 mobile device”、“听力装置 listening device”。“Device” 是可数名词。来听一个例句。&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Example:&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;All mobile devices should be switched off during this flight.
请在本次飞行中关闭所有移动设备。&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;a water-saving device
节水装置&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;electrical labour-saving devices around the home
节省劳力的各种家用电器&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;equipment:&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;单词 “equipment” 表示 “特定活动所需的设备、器械”，是不可数名词。如果想说 “一件设备”，我们可以在 “equipment” 前搭配 “a piece of 一个，一件”，即 “a piece of equipment”。&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;“Equipment” 通常指 “成套的，不只一件的设备”。而且，与 “device” 和 “appliance” 不同的是，“equipment” 不光包括 “电子设备”，还包含相关的工具。比如，上文提到的 “cycling and diving equipment 自行车和潜水装备” 中可能包括服装、自行车灯、潜水眼镜、呼吸器等物品；再如，“医疗设备” 的说法是 “medical equipment”。比如，虽然 “听诊器 stethoscope” 是一种 “medical equipment”，但它并不是一个 “medical device”，因为听诊器不是电子的。&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Example:&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;The hospital has been donated medical equipment that’s worth a million pounds.
这家医院收到了价值一百万英镑的医疗设备捐助。&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;The plant was dismantled of all its equipment and furniture.
这家工厂的设备和家具全被拆除了。&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;tool:&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;一般指进行特种工作的手工工具，也可指人造使用动力的工具，还可作引申用。&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;I find the best tool for the purpose is a pair of shears.
我发现做这件事最得力的工具是一把大剪刀。&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;implement:&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;原指史前人类所用的工具，现在多指农用工具，也可指为实现某个任务所需的工具或器具。&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;knives and other useful implements
刀子和其他有用工具&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;installation:&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;一般多指安装完成，可供使用或操作的整套装置或设施。&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;The building was turned into a secret military installation.
该建筑被改造成了一处秘密军事设施。&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;appliance:&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;侧重指家用机器或设备，尤指家用电器。&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;可数名词 “appliance”。“Appliance” 尤指 “家用电器 home appliances”，比如冰箱、烤箱、洗衣机等等。通常，冰箱本身并不是 “装置 device”，但我们可以把控制家电的 “智能家居设备” 叫做 “home device”。&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;Examples:&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;The shopping channel is known for selling home appliances.
这个购物频道以卖家电出名。&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;I can switch on my oven remotely using the new home device.
我可以用这台新型智能家居装置来远程打开家里的烤箱。&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;He could also learn to use the vacuum cleaner, the washing machine and other household appliances.
他可以再学学使用吸尘器、洗衣机和其他家用电器。&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;facilities:&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;常用复数形式，指可供使用的设备或设施。&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Medical facilities are being reorganized and upgraded.
正在对医疗设施进行重组和升级。&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;

    &lt;blockquote&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;Our city needs more facilities for recreation.
我们城市需要更多的娱乐设施。&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/blockquote&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;再来一个例子：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Jimmy just moved into his new flat and is ready to unpack. First, he put away his clothes, his mobile devices, his cycling and diving equipment, and then he put all his books on the shelf. The flat is equipped with household appliances such as a fridge, a freezer, an oven, a dishwasher, a washing machine, a TV, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Jimmy 刚刚搬进他的新公寓，正准备整理行李。他先收好了衣物、移动设备，放好了他的自行车和潜水装备，并把所有的书都摆上书架。这间公寓备有冰箱、冰柜、烤箱、洗碗机、洗衣机、电视等生活家电。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="English" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Activity, Motion, Motive, Motivation, Motivate 区别</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/english-activity-motion-motive-motivation-motivate/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Activity, Motion, Motive, Motivation, Motivate 区别" /><published>2020-01-03T00:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2020-01-03T00:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/english-activity-motion-motive-motivation-motivate</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/english-activity-motion-motive-motivation-motivate/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://hips.hearstapps.com/hmg-prod.s3.amazonaws.com/images/rw0115yea-07-1545343575.jpg?crop=1.00xw:0.676xh;0,0.199xh&amp;amp;resize=2048:*&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- more --&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Activity
    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;活跃、繁忙( Uncountable) &lt;em&gt;the situation in which a lot of things are happening or people are moving around&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;行动、活动 &lt;em&gt;the work of a group or organization to achieve an aim&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;娱乐活动 &lt;em&gt;something that is done for enjoyment, especially an organized event&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;There was a lot of activity in preparation for the Queen’s visit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;He was found guilty of terrorist activity. / criminal activities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;His spare-time activities include cooking, tennis, and windsurfing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Motion&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;动、运动、移动 &lt;em&gt;the act or process of moving, or a particular action or movement&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;They showed the goal again in slow motion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Motive
动机 &lt;em&gt;a reason for doing something&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Why would she have killed him? She has no motive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Motivation
    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;积极性、干劲儿 &lt;em&gt;enthusiasm for doing something&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;动机、诱因 &lt;em&gt;the need or reason for doing something&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;He’s a bright enough student - he just lacks motivation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;What was the motivation for the attack?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Motivate
    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;使产生动机、激起 &lt;em&gt;to cause someone to behave in a particular way&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;激励 &lt;em&gt;to make someone want to do something well&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Like so many people, he’s motivated by greed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Teaching is all about motivating people to learn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="English" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>